<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Social Justice on Jessica S. Marquis</title>
    <link>http://example.org/tags/social-justice/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Social Justice on Jessica S. Marquis</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2017 21:25:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/tags/social-justice/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Poop-Talk Embargo and Its Fallout</title>
      <link>http://example.org/2017/11/03/2017-11-the-poop-talk-embargo-and-its-fallout-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2017 21:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/2017/11/03/2017-11-the-poop-talk-embargo-and-its-fallout-html/</guid>
      <description>We recently instituted a ban on the word &amp;#8220;poop&amp;#8221; &amp;#8211; and all its variants &amp;#8211; while eating meals. Naturally, our oldest had lots of questions to determine loopholes, because that is what she does. She&amp;#8217;s a negotiator, and even at age 5 she wants to determine all the gray areas. She&amp;#8217;s already learned that a rule can be bent or circumvented.


Since Bob and I do not have unlimited reserves of patience and creativity, we issued a plain statement that any use of the word would land the speaker in her/his room for a time out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snowflake Vigil: A How-To for Grief and Young Ones</title>
      <link>http://example.org/2016/06/17/2016-06-snowflake-vigil-how-to-for-grief-and-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2016 23:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/2016/06/17/2016-06-snowflake-vigil-how-to-for-grief-and-html/</guid>
      <description>I mentioned in an earlier post that I may do a &amp;#8220;snowflake vigil&amp;#8221; with my kiddos, all under age 4, regarding the tragic mass shooting at Pulse, a gay club in Orlando. It&amp;#8217;s critical to start an ongoing conversation with them even now about loving others, respecting all, and advocacy. If we claim to love Jesus, whose heart was all about justice, we need to also claim verses like this one:&amp;nbsp; _</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Too Close to Define</title>
      <link>http://example.org/2016/03/25/2016-03-too-close-to-define-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2016 02:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/2016/03/25/2016-03-too-close-to-define-html/</guid>
      <description>You know that experience when you&amp;#8217;re so close to something you can&amp;#8217;t really say anything about it? When it&amp;#8217;s feels like you&amp;#8217;re trying to build something and discover you&amp;#8217;re using water instead of packing snow? When you&amp;#8217;re afraid a remark about it would only touch part and miss the whole?
I remember someone joking that if you need the definition of &amp;#8220;psychology&amp;#8221;, you should [counterintuitively] ask the first-semester psych major, not the PhD clinician.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>