<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pain on Jessica S. Marquis</title>
    <link>http://dev.jessicasmarquis.com/tags/pain/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pain on Jessica S. Marquis</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2016 03:35:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://dev.jessicasmarquis.com/tags/pain/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>My Ambivalent Fallout with a Bush: A Story of Unexpected Restoration</title>
      <link>http://dev.jessicasmarquis.com/posts/2016-10-18-my-ambivalent-fallout-with-bush-story/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2016 03:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dev.jessicasmarquis.com/posts/2016-10-18-my-ambivalent-fallout-with-bush-story/</guid>
      <description>Last December, we had our front and back yards turned into desert landscaping. They went from being full of dirt, weeds, a big mulberry tree that pigeons pooped from, and a thorny bougainvillea, to being full of rocks, desert plants, a smaller tree that pigeons disdain, and a wispy bush with orange flowers.
We were enamored.
And then the weeds started. They got out of control. We tried to fight them, but we had to have professionals come in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Presumptive Pain-Sharing</title>
      <link>http://dev.jessicasmarquis.com/posts/2016-06-16-presumptive-pain-sharing.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2016 22:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dev.jessicasmarquis.com/posts/2016-06-16-presumptive-pain-sharing.1/</guid>
      <description>Lesson I&amp;#8217;ve witnessed over and over: It may seem the same to you, but don&amp;#8217;t assume you know what the other person is feeling. Doing so is like a slap to the face.
Here is the Hierarchy of Face Slaps that tend to commence once someone has made that assumption:
 They say, &amp;#8220;I know what you&amp;#8217;re feeling.&amp;#8221;
 They hijack the conversation to share their story.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Of Obstacles and Birdsongs</title>
      <link>http://dev.jessicasmarquis.com/posts/2016-05-05-of-obstacles-and-birdsongs/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 18:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dev.jessicasmarquis.com/posts/2016-05-05-of-obstacles-and-birdsongs/</guid>
      <description>In all my experience with obeying Christ &amp;#8211; and with disobeying Him &amp;#8211; I have become convinced that when we get serious about following Him, things get harder. Life gets uglier. Obstacles appear out of nowhere, and we wonder if maybe we messed up or maybe it isn&amp;#8217;t worth it to keep going.
This has become all the more true since I&amp;#8217;ve fully committed to the ministry my Shepherd called me into.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>