<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sacrifice on Jessica S. Marquis</title>
    <link>http://dev.jessicasmarquis.com/tags/sacrifice/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Sacrifice on Jessica S. Marquis</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2016 22:59:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://dev.jessicasmarquis.com/tags/sacrifice/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Cover Charge</title>
      <link>http://dev.jessicasmarquis.com/post/2016/10/cover-charge/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2016 22:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dev.jessicasmarquis.com/post/2016/10/cover-charge/</guid>
      <description>I was never much of a clubber. In my late teens and early twenties, I liked going dancing with my friends on occasion, but my dancing was more entertaining than sexy so I didn&amp;#8217;t fit in at many venues. Plus, most of them were smoker friendly back then, and drinks cost a hefty fraction of my paycheck. (There weren&amp;#8217;t many people who wanted to buy a drink for the gal using coffee stirrers as glow sticks during the remix of Ben Folds Five&amp;#8217;s &amp;#8220;Brick&amp;#8221; &amp;#8211; which, by the way, whose awful idea was that to create a club version of a tragic abortion song?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Countdown</title>
      <link>http://dev.jessicasmarquis.com/post/2016/01/the-countdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2016 22:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dev.jessicasmarquis.com/post/2016/01/the-countdown/</guid>
      <description>In less than 48 hours, I will be entering a modified Daniel Fast. There is nothing magical about this type of fast; I think it’s just more accessible for many of us. Because I’m still breastfeeding twin boys several times a day, I’m not going to complicate my life by changing this family’s entire diet for 10 days. That would inevitably turn the fast itself into an idol, as I’d scurry about the kitchen picking my brain and the mass brain of the internet for recipes and nutritional considerations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>From the other side of the chrysalis</title>
      <link>http://dev.jessicasmarquis.com/post/2015/12/from-the-other-side-of-the-chrysalis/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2015 16:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dev.jessicasmarquis.com/post/2015/12/from-the-other-side-of-the-chrysalis/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;#8217;ve had a few weeks to process the dissolution of our weekly Milkweed Momdays. This past Monday was the first without the Bible study written on my calendar. (To be more accurate, it was written on the calendar, but I crossed it off.)
Through reflections both in solitude and in the safe exploration afforded by the presence of gentle and wise friends, my perspective is widening beyond the sacrifice of my &amp;#8220;baby&amp;#8221; on that mountain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cocoons</title>
      <link>http://dev.jessicasmarquis.com/post/2015/11/cocoons/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2015 19:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dev.jessicasmarquis.com/post/2015/11/cocoons/</guid>
      <description>On November 1 of this year, I wrote in my journal, &amp;#8220;I feel like something is about to turn.&amp;#8221;
The next day, we met for our weekly Milkweed Momday and launched one of our own monarch butterflies, a mama named Jamie, out of our milkweed and into her new adventure.
&amp;#8220;How exciting,&amp;#8221; I mused to my Shepherd. &amp;#8220;Now, what&amp;#8217;s next?&amp;#8221;
I felt Him inviting me up a mountain. It looked like a beautiful hike.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>