<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Church on Jessica S. Marquis</title>
    <link>http://dev.jessicasmarquis.com/tags/church/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Church on Jessica S. Marquis</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2017 22:51:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://dev.jessicasmarquis.com/tags/church/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The In-Between</title>
      <link>http://dev.jessicasmarquis.com/2017/04/the-in-between/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2017 22:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dev.jessicasmarquis.com/2017/04/the-in-between/</guid>
      <description>We are currently church orphans. I guess that term is preferable to church shoppers, and it feels more emotionally appropriate because we left our church after discovering it was moving in a different direction from us. To be blunt, it felt like it had already left us, and we had just received the news.
This post isn&amp;#8217;t about our former church. We love our family there and the work they are doing in the name of our Savior in the city and world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Church, Please!</title>
      <link>http://dev.jessicasmarquis.com/2016/11/church-please/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2016 23:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dev.jessicasmarquis.com/2016/11/church-please/</guid>
      <description>Dear Bride of Christ,
I love you with a relentless passion that I can&amp;#8217;t abandon no matter how ugly or derisive you become. You are the creation and beloved of my Beloved, and so I am inseparably part of you. So, since I can&amp;#8217;t leave (which is what I&amp;#8217;m best trained in doing), I need to have a literal &amp;#8220;Come to Jesus&amp;#8221; chat with you.
You &amp;#8211; we &amp;#8211; have forgotten our First Love.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>days #15-#18</title>
      <link>http://dev.jessicasmarquis.com/2010/01/days-#15-%2318/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2010 16:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dev.jessicasmarquis.com/2010/01/days-#15-%2318/</guid>
      <description>three-day weekends throw me for a loop.
when i was younger, a day off meant VACATION!
now, it means having more time for organizing, errand-running, &amp;amp; homework.
my to-do list for today looks nothing like a passion-igniter.
but yesterday&amp;#8217;s message at our church certainly was.
after talking about how our small expectations can get in the way of God actually creating something awesome &amp;#8212;
or, at least, get in the way of us appreciating it</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>day #3 &amp; #4</title>
      <link>http://dev.jessicasmarquis.com/2010/01/day-#3--%234/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2010 14:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dev.jessicasmarquis.com/2010/01/day-#3--%234/</guid>
      <description>yesterday, we visited our friends&amp;#8217; church, poiema, one much closer to us than the one we&amp;#8217;ve been attending in north phoenix.
it was odd doing this, as we&amp;#8217;ve been going to PVCC since we moved here, and we&amp;#8217;ve made some great friends there.
still, we were interested in checking out poiema &amp;amp; meeting some new people.
and for those of us who know genesis, our church back in royal oak, you&amp;#8217;d know how at home we felt when we found out the following:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>