<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Community on Jessica S. Marquis</title>
    <link>http://dev.jessicasmarquis.com/tags/community/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Community on Jessica S. Marquis</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2016 22:48:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://dev.jessicasmarquis.com/tags/community/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Casting CAST</title>
      <link>http://dev.jessicasmarquis.com/post/2016/04/casting-cast/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2016 22:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dev.jessicasmarquis.com/post/2016/04/casting-cast/</guid>
      <description>The general consensus was that no one&amp;#8217;s husband thought they should be there.
With a theme like &amp;#8220;Busyness&amp;#8221;, it&amp;#8217;s hard to find a woman who can speak to the topic as an expert at managing it. And even if she does exist, none of us could relate to her, which was what the event was about.
These women were sitting in confession via a stage in front of a couple dozen of their sisters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Too Close to Define</title>
      <link>http://dev.jessicasmarquis.com/post/2016/03/too-close-to-define/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2016 02:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dev.jessicasmarquis.com/post/2016/03/too-close-to-define/</guid>
      <description>You know that experience when you&amp;#8217;re so close to something you can&amp;#8217;t really say anything about it? When it&amp;#8217;s feels like you&amp;#8217;re trying to build something and discover you&amp;#8217;re using water instead of packing snow? When you&amp;#8217;re afraid a remark about it would only touch part and miss the whole?
I remember someone joking that if you need the definition of &amp;#8220;psychology&amp;#8221;, you should [counterintuitively] ask the first-semester psych major, not the PhD clinician.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Commentary Track</title>
      <link>http://dev.jessicasmarquis.com/post/2016/03/the-commentary-track/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 18:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dev.jessicasmarquis.com/post/2016/03/the-commentary-track/</guid>
      <description>I recently came across a sort of time capsule that perfectly exemplified where I was at during that point in my spiritual life. Rarely does a time capsule perfectly fulfill what it&amp;#8217;s supposed to do &amp;#8211; make the recipient into a time traveler &amp;#8211; but this one put me squarely in my thought process of 2009 Jessica.
The item was a treatment for an animation I was proposing at that time for my friend, Kristen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Countdown</title>
      <link>http://dev.jessicasmarquis.com/post/2016/01/the-countdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2016 22:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dev.jessicasmarquis.com/post/2016/01/the-countdown/</guid>
      <description>In less than 48 hours, I will be entering a modified Daniel Fast. There is nothing magical about this type of fast; I think it’s just more accessible for many of us. Because I’m still breastfeeding twin boys several times a day, I’m not going to complicate my life by changing this family’s entire diet for 10 days. That would inevitably turn the fast itself into an idol, as I’d scurry about the kitchen picking my brain and the mass brain of the internet for recipes and nutritional considerations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cocoons</title>
      <link>http://dev.jessicasmarquis.com/post/2015/11/cocoons/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2015 19:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dev.jessicasmarquis.com/post/2015/11/cocoons/</guid>
      <description>On November 1 of this year, I wrote in my journal, &amp;#8220;I feel like something is about to turn.&amp;#8221;
The next day, we met for our weekly Milkweed Momday and launched one of our own monarch butterflies, a mama named Jamie, out of our milkweed and into her new adventure.
&amp;#8220;How exciting,&amp;#8221; I mused to my Shepherd. &amp;#8220;Now, what&amp;#8217;s next?&amp;#8221;
I felt Him inviting me up a mountain. It looked like a beautiful hike.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>From a mom of 3 under 4 to the incoming grad school student</title>
      <link>http://dev.jessicasmarquis.com/post/2015/09/from-a-mom-of-3-under-4-to-the-incoming-grad-school-student/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2015 00:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dev.jessicasmarquis.com/post/2015/09/from-a-mom-of-3-under-4-to-the-incoming-grad-school-student/</guid>
      <description>Below is a letter I posted at my new blog, Verses 3 to 5, where Christian women can post letters to their former selves. God&amp;#8217;s grace is so good!
Dear 22-year-old Jessy,
First of all, I know how closed you are to advice, especially any that comes from someone who approaches you with an attitude of, &amp;#8220;I&amp;#8217;m older, so I know.&amp;#8221; It seems condescending, and I will strive to avoid that here.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>