<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Rest on Jessica S. Marquis</title>
    <link>http://dev.jessicasmarquis.com/tags/rest/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Rest on Jessica S. Marquis</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 18:25:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://dev.jessicasmarquis.com/tags/rest/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Of Obstacles and Birdsongs</title>
      <link>http://dev.jessicasmarquis.com/posts/2016-05-05-of-obstacles-and-birdsongs/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 18:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dev.jessicasmarquis.com/posts/2016-05-05-of-obstacles-and-birdsongs/</guid>
      <description>In all my experience with obeying Christ &amp;#8211; and with disobeying Him &amp;#8211; I have become convinced that when we get serious about following Him, things get harder. Life gets uglier. Obstacles appear out of nowhere, and we wonder if maybe we messed up or maybe it isn&amp;#8217;t worth it to keep going.
This has become all the more true since I&amp;#8217;ve fully committed to the ministry my Shepherd called me into.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>day #2</title>
      <link>http://dev.jessicasmarquis.com/posts/2010-01-02-day-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2010 16:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dev.jessicasmarquis.com/posts/2010-01-02-day-2/</guid>
      <description>it&amp;#8217;s not so much that i was craving tea.
often my cravings force me into a no-nonsense beeline, and, since this was more of a leisurely sunday drive on a friday afternoon, all signs point to no craving.
no, what i was after was more the process than the result. so i embarked on a mini-adventure up the 51, next to the mountains that pop up &amp;amp; appear to swallow cars at shea, heading toward the artsy pedestrian bridges south of greenway.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>in motion &amp; out of strength</title>
      <link>http://dev.jessicasmarquis.com/posts/2008-10-22-in-motion-out-of-strength/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2008 05:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dev.jessicasmarquis.com/posts/2008-10-22-in-motion-out-of-strength/</guid>
      <description>i heard a comment today that really stuck with me:
God doesn&amp;#8217;t give strength to us when we&amp;#8217;re in motion.
the context of this is NOT that God doesn&amp;#8217;t help us when we have a lot going on.
in fact, the person who said it remarked that God always makes sure we won&amp;#8217;t run out of steam when we are under pressure.
the context of this statement IS that we need to be taking time to be still before God,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>title of the song</title>
      <link>http://dev.jessicasmarquis.com/posts/2008-08-07-title-of-song/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2008 03:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dev.jessicasmarquis.com/posts/2008-08-07-title-of-song/</guid>
      <description>why would someone who is allergic to cottonwood consider it a blessing?
that&amp;#8217;s what i asked in order to get this exclusive interview&amp;#8230;with myself.
Q: what&amp;#8217;s the story behind the title?
A: i was on a walk in my neighborhood several years ago, frustrated with the pain i was in &amp;amp; my perception of God&amp;#8217;s lack of intervention. i kept chasing after His approval &amp;amp; His gifts, and i came up empty-handed.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>