<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Lgbtq on Jessica S. Marquis</title>
    <link>http://example.org/tags/lgbtq/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Lgbtq on Jessica S. Marquis</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2017 22:51:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/tags/lgbtq/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The In-Between</title>
      <link>http://example.org/2017/04/19/2017-04-the-in-between-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2017 22:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/2017/04/19/2017-04-the-in-between-html/</guid>
      <description>We are currently church orphans. I guess that term is preferable to church shoppers, and it feels more emotionally appropriate because we left our church after discovering it was moving in a different direction from us. To be blunt, it felt like it had already left us, and we had just received the news.
This post isn&amp;#8217;t about our former church. We love our family there and the work they are doing in the name of our Savior in the city and world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snowflake Vigil: A How-To for Grief and Young Ones</title>
      <link>http://example.org/2016/06/17/2016-06-snowflake-vigil-how-to-for-grief-and-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2016 23:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/2016/06/17/2016-06-snowflake-vigil-how-to-for-grief-and-html/</guid>
      <description>I mentioned in an earlier post that I may do a &amp;#8220;snowflake vigil&amp;#8221; with my kiddos, all under age 4, regarding the tragic mass shooting at Pulse, a gay club in Orlando. It&amp;#8217;s critical to start an ongoing conversation with them even now about loving others, respecting all, and advocacy. If we claim to love Jesus, whose heart was all about justice, we need to also claim verses like this one:&amp;nbsp; _</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snowflake Vigil</title>
      <link>http://example.org/2016/06/13/2016-06-snowflake-vigil-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2016 20:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/2016/06/13/2016-06-snowflake-vigil-html/</guid>
      <description>Sadness isn&amp;#8217;t an easy feeling for us. Anger is easy because it&amp;#8217;s in motion. It helps us feel like we&amp;#8217;re doing something. But sadness has a purpose &amp;#8211; if nothing else, &amp;#8216;Inside Out&amp;#8217; should have taught us that.
Yes, we need to be angry about what happened yesterday in Orlando. I&amp;#8217;m pissed like a bee-stung mama bear that anyone would so brutally harm my fellow beloved creations of God, that my LGBTQ brothers &amp;amp; sisters yet again feel victimized.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>