<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Progress on Jessica S. Marquis</title>
    <link>http://dev.jessicasmarquis.com/tags/progress/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Progress on Jessica S. Marquis</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2017 23:43:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://dev.jessicasmarquis.com/tags/progress/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Hard-won advice from a reluctant event organizer and project manager</title>
      <link>http://dev.jessicasmarquis.com/post/2017/09/hard-won-advice-from-a-reluctant-event-organizer-and-project-manager/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2017 23:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dev.jessicasmarquis.com/post/2017/09/hard-won-advice-from-a-reluctant-event-organizer-and-project-manager/</guid>
      <description>When I was in middle school, I got the itch to organize events. No, that&amp;#8217;s inaccurate. I realized the need for organization, so I did it. There wasn&amp;#8217;t really an itch, just a desire to get to the end goal and no bridges provided to it. The point is, I got started in event creation and project management shortly after I hit the double digits, so I have a little bit of experience in it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>day #7</title>
      <link>http://dev.jessicasmarquis.com/post/2010/01/day-#7/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2010 15:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dev.jessicasmarquis.com/post/2010/01/day-#7/</guid>
      <description>we ripped 3 links off the blue paper chain hanging in our bedroom this morning. the chain represents our debt, each link being $1,000.
there was a time in my life when spending $1,000 was an absurd thought. however, i came into this marriage with
$7,000 of debt that i owed on my car + $5,000 remaining on my school loan. ____________ $12,000 in the hole.
add that to what bob had being a homeowner with a mortgage, and our chain was too long for us not to notice it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>day #3 &amp; #4</title>
      <link>http://dev.jessicasmarquis.com/post/2010/01/day-#3--%234/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2010 14:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dev.jessicasmarquis.com/post/2010/01/day-#3--%234/</guid>
      <description>yesterday, we visited our friends&amp;#8217; church, poiema, one much closer to us than the one we&amp;#8217;ve been attending in north phoenix.
it was odd doing this, as we&amp;#8217;ve been going to PVCC since we moved here, and we&amp;#8217;ve made some great friends there.
still, we were interested in checking out poiema &amp;amp; meeting some new people.
and for those of us who know genesis, our church back in royal oak, you&amp;#8217;d know how at home we felt when we found out the following:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>