<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jessica S. Marquis</title>
    <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Jessica S. Marquis</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2017 21:25:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://jess.bobmarquis.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Poop-Talk Embargo and Its Fallout</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2017/11/03/2017-11-the-poop-talk-embargo-and-its-fallout-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2017 21:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2017/11/03/2017-11-the-poop-talk-embargo-and-its-fallout-html/</guid>
      <description>We recently instituted a ban on the word &amp;#8220;poop&amp;#8221; &amp;#8211; and all its variants &amp;#8211; while eating meals. Naturally, our oldest had lots of questions to determine loopholes, because that is what she does. She&amp;#8217;s a negotiator, and even at age 5 she wants to determine all the gray areas. She&amp;#8217;s already learned that a rule can be bent or circumvented.
Since Bob and I do not have unlimited reserves of patience and creativity, we issued a plain statement that any use of the word would land the speaker in her/his room for a time out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hard-won advice from a reluctant event organizer and project manager</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2017/09/19/2017-09-hard-won-advice-from-reluctant-event-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2017 23:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2017/09/19/2017-09-hard-won-advice-from-reluctant-event-html/</guid>
      <description>When I was in middle school, I got the itch to organize events. No, that&amp;#8217;s inaccurate. I realized the need for organization, so I did it. There wasn&amp;#8217;t really an itch, just a desire to get to the end goal and no bridges provided to it. The point is, I got started in event creation and project management shortly after I hit the double digits, so I have a little bit of experience in it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Permission Slip to Deconstruct</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2017/04/27/2017-04-a-permission-slip-to-deconstruct-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2017 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2017/04/27/2017-04-a-permission-slip-to-deconstruct-html/</guid>
      <description>Truth ought to come with this disclaimer:
&amp;#8220;This will not fit right at first. You may find your reality shifting, and all you trusted slipping through your fingers. That is okay. Just press onward and rest in the uncertainty.&amp;#8221;
I&amp;#8217;m writing this because no one gave me that disclaimer. I&amp;#8217;m writing this for the people who have started asking big questions or who are seeing things they didn&amp;#8217;t used to, who are finding they aren&amp;#8217;t who they used to be and think they might just be going crazy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The In-Between</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2017/04/19/2017-04-the-in-between-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2017 22:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2017/04/19/2017-04-the-in-between-html/</guid>
      <description>We are currently church orphans. I guess that term is preferable to church shoppers, and it feels more emotionally appropriate because we left our church after discovering it was moving in a different direction from us. To be blunt, it felt like it had already left us, and we had just received the news.
This post isn&amp;#8217;t about our former church. We love our family there and the work they are doing in the name of our Savior in the city and world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thick Skin and the Girl Who Doesn’t Have It</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2017/03/05/2017-03-the-unexpected-discomfort-of-waking-up-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2017 20:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2017/03/05/2017-03-the-unexpected-discomfort-of-waking-up-html/</guid>
      <description>“I’m not political,” I said.
“Must be nice,” she replied.
Know what’s weird about this conversation? I don’t remember with whom I was speaking. It has transcended an actual setting and characters. All I recall is that I was in a majority class &amp;#8211; white, Christian, straight, able-bodied, whatever &amp;#8211; and my friend was not.
This simple dialogue has taken place in various ways on more than one occasion, boring itself deeper and deeper into my psyche, each time convicting me that I enjoy privilege I have not earned.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why my kids may have a lot of hospital visits OR The undervalued gift of doubt</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2017/02/05/2017-02-why-my-kids-may-have-lot-of-hospital-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2017 20:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2017/02/05/2017-02-why-my-kids-may-have-lot-of-hospital-html/</guid>
      <description>I gripped her hand in mine, adrenaline surging, eyes unblinking, reluctant to look at the bloody mess that likely lay within.
“Never!” I exclaimed with more force than I expected. The fear was shoving words out. “Never grab at the food Mama is slicing!”
Yanking my hand open, my pupils fixated on her thumb. I scanned it for flaps of flesh. Nothing. Masking my relief, I looked up at her eyes that were as wide as mine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Church, Please!</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2016/11/11/2016-11-church-please-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2016 23:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2016/11/11/2016-11-church-please-html/</guid>
      <description>Dear Bride of Christ,
I love you with a relentless passion that I can&amp;#8217;t abandon no matter how ugly or derisive you become. You are the creation and beloved of my Beloved, and so I am inseparably part of you. So, since I can&amp;#8217;t leave (which is what I&amp;#8217;m best trained in doing), I need to have a literal &amp;#8220;Come to Jesus&amp;#8221; chat with you.
You &amp;#8211; we &amp;#8211; have forgotten our First Love.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Excavating Accidentally Buried Talents</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2016/11/07/2016-11-excavating-accidentally-buried-talents-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2016 03:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2016/11/07/2016-11-excavating-accidentally-buried-talents-html/</guid>
      <description>&amp;#8220;All meat, no parsley.&amp;#8221;
I&amp;#8217;ve never been labeled a carnivore, but I love that phrase. It describes my thinking, and why I don&amp;#8217;t like reading most blogs &amp;#8211; or writing them very often.
The metaphor was uttered at Prism :: Gifts, an event I attended yesterday for women wanting to discover their spiritual gifts and how to use them. It was glorious in the way spending a day with open-hearted sisters who want to be real and effective is glorious.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Ambivalent Fallout with a Bush: A Story of Unexpected Restoration</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2016/10/18/2016-10-my-ambivalent-fallout-with-bush-story-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2016 03:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2016/10/18/2016-10-my-ambivalent-fallout-with-bush-story-html/</guid>
      <description>Last December, we had our front and back yards turned into desert landscaping. They went from being full of dirt, weeds, a big mulberry tree that pigeons pooped from, and a thorny bougainvillea, to being full of rocks, desert plants, a smaller tree that pigeons disdain, and a wispy bush with orange flowers.
We were enamored.
And then the weeds started. They got out of control. We tried to fight them, but we had to have professionals come in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cover Charge</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2016/10/07/2016-10-cover-charge-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2016 22:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2016/10/07/2016-10-cover-charge-html/</guid>
      <description>I was never much of a clubber. In my late teens and early twenties, I liked going dancing with my friends on occasion, but my dancing was more entertaining than sexy so I didn&amp;#8217;t fit in at many venues. Plus, most of them were smoker friendly back then, and drinks cost a hefty fraction of my paycheck. (There weren&amp;#8217;t many people who wanted to buy a drink for the gal using coffee stirrers as glow sticks during the remix of Ben Folds Five&amp;#8217;s &amp;#8220;Brick&amp;#8221; &amp;#8211; which, by the way, whose awful idea was that to create a club version of a tragic abortion song?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where Are My Eagle Wings?</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2016/08/20/2016-08-where-are-my-eagle-wings-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2016 18:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2016/08/20/2016-08-where-are-my-eagle-wings-html/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;#8217;m working hard on CAST #2: Restoration, an event for women focusing on both brokenness &amp;amp; God&amp;#8217;s restorative vision for creation. My personal drama is this: I&amp;#8217;m currently in a complicated relationship with restoration.
As I&amp;#8217;ve previously written, I recently went through a confusingly dry season of waiting &amp;amp; clinging. It&amp;#8217;s been jet-black darkness at countless times, with equally innumerable false-starts of returning to daylight.
All the while, I&amp;#8217;ve been holding to the hope-inflating notion that when I reach daylight there will be a tangible sense of restoration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Uncle Mark’s Troublesome Toy Car</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2016/06/26/2016-06-uncle-marks-troublesome-toy-car-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2016 20:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2016/06/26/2016-06-uncle-marks-troublesome-toy-car-html/</guid>
      <description>For those of you who have set a boundary with a loved one and need a way to communicate about it to your young children, feel free to use the story below which I wrote for our little ones. Due to the tragic passing of my brother after his battle with addiction, we no longer need it; still, I want to share it with anyone who may.
Uncle Mark’s Troublesome Toy Car:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snowflake Vigil: A How-To for Grief and Young Ones</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2016/06/17/2016-06-snowflake-vigil-how-to-for-grief-and-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2016 23:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2016/06/17/2016-06-snowflake-vigil-how-to-for-grief-and-html/</guid>
      <description>I mentioned in an earlier post that I may do a &amp;#8220;snowflake vigil&amp;#8221; with my kiddos, all under age 4, regarding the tragic mass shooting at Pulse, a gay club in Orlando. It&amp;#8217;s critical to start an ongoing conversation with them even now about loving others, respecting all, and advocacy. If we claim to love Jesus, whose heart was all about justice, we need to also claim verses like this one: _ _</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Presumptive Pain-Sharing</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2016/06/16/2016-06-presumptive-pain-sharing-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2016 22:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2016/06/16/2016-06-presumptive-pain-sharing-html/</guid>
      <description>Lesson I&amp;#8217;ve witnessed over and over: It may seem the same to you, but don&amp;#8217;t assume you know what the other person is feeling. Doing so is like a slap to the face.
Here is the Hierarchy of Face Slaps that tend to commence once someone has made that assumption:
 They say, &amp;#8220;I know what you&amp;#8217;re feeling.&amp;#8221;
 They hijack the conversation to share their story.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Forgotten Storylines: How Sitcoms Taught Me that God Has a Grand Narrative</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2016/06/14/2016-06-forgotten-storylines-how-sitcoms-taught-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2016 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2016/06/14/2016-06-forgotten-storylines-how-sitcoms-taught-html/</guid>
      <description>In my mind, there are two types of comedy shows: The kind that build a cohesive storyline throughout the episodes, and the kind where each episode is its own story. I&amp;#8217;m sure they have industry terms, but I don&amp;#8217;t want to stop my brain dump to research them. Let&amp;#8217;s just call the former Arrested Development and the latter The Simpsons.
If you watch an episode of Arrested Development and then jump ahead a few episodes, you may be confused by why the lawyer is a different guy, or find yourself asking what happened to Marta or Gob&amp;#8217;s puppet Franklin or Charlize Theron and her fantastic fashions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snowflake Vigil</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2016/06/13/2016-06-snowflake-vigil-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2016 20:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2016/06/13/2016-06-snowflake-vigil-html/</guid>
      <description>Sadness isn&amp;#8217;t an easy feeling for us. Anger is easy because it&amp;#8217;s in motion. It helps us feel like we&amp;#8217;re doing something. But sadness has a purpose &amp;#8211; if nothing else, &amp;#8216;Inside Out&amp;#8217; should have taught us that.
Yes, we need to be angry about what happened yesterday in Orlando. I&amp;#8217;m pissed like a bee-stung mama bear that anyone would so brutally harm my fellow beloved creations of God, that my LGBTQ brothers &amp;amp; sisters yet again feel victimized.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Confessions of an Idol-Worshiper</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2016/05/26/2016-05-confessions-of-idol-worshiper-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2016 17:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2016/05/26/2016-05-confessions-of-idol-worshiper-html/</guid>
      <description>Once upon a time, people worshiped idols. They were made of wood or clay or stone. They looked like creatures, and they couldn&amp;#8217;t do anything. These ancient people were silly for thinking the idols could help them. Now, we are so much better and smarter, and we don&amp;#8217;t have idols.
This was the story I told myself growing up in the Church.
And then my Sunday school teacher informed me TV could be an idol.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Of Obstacles and Birdsongs</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2016/05/05/2016-05-of-obstacles-and-birdsongs-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 18:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2016/05/05/2016-05-of-obstacles-and-birdsongs-html/</guid>
      <description>In all my experience with obeying Christ &amp;#8211; and with disobeying Him &amp;#8211; I have become convinced that when we get serious about following Him, things get harder. Life gets uglier. Obstacles appear out of nowhere, and we wonder if maybe we messed up or maybe it isn&amp;#8217;t worth it to keep going.
This has become all the more true since I&amp;#8217;ve fully committed to the ministry my Shepherd called me into.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Casting CAST</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2016/04/24/2016-04-casting-cast-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2016 22:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2016/04/24/2016-04-casting-cast-html/</guid>
      <description>The general consensus was that no one&amp;#8217;s husband thought they should be there.
With a theme like &amp;#8220;Busyness&amp;#8221;, it&amp;#8217;s hard to find a woman who can speak to the topic as an expert at managing it. And even if she does exist, none of us could relate to her, which was what the event was about.
These women were sitting in confession via a stage in front of a couple dozen of their sisters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Too Close to Define</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2016/03/25/2016-03-too-close-to-define-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2016 02:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2016/03/25/2016-03-too-close-to-define-html/</guid>
      <description>You know that experience when you&amp;#8217;re so close to something you can&amp;#8217;t really say anything about it? When it&amp;#8217;s feels like you&amp;#8217;re trying to build something and discover you&amp;#8217;re using water instead of packing snow? When you&amp;#8217;re afraid a remark about it would only touch part and miss the whole?
I remember someone joking that if you need the definition of &amp;#8220;psychology&amp;#8221;, you should [counterintuitively] ask the first-semester psych major, not the PhD clinician.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Commentary Track</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2016/03/09/2016-03-the-commentary-track-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 18:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2016/03/09/2016-03-the-commentary-track-html/</guid>
      <description>I recently came across a sort of time capsule that perfectly exemplified where I was at during that point in my spiritual life. Rarely does a time capsule perfectly fulfill what it&amp;#8217;s supposed to do &amp;#8211; make the recipient into a time traveler &amp;#8211; but this one put me squarely in my thought process of 2009 Jessica.
The item was a treatment for an animation I was proposing at that time for my friend, Kristen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Waiting for the Taxi</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2016/02/06/2016-02-waiting-for-taxi-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2016 21:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2016/02/06/2016-02-waiting-for-taxi-html/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;#8217;s taken me a long time to learn forgiveness is not contingent on the other&amp;#8217;s apology. To refuse to forgive until the other says sorry is like refusing to go to work until someone sends a taxi for me, even though I have my own car.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On Spiritual Gluttony</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2016/01/16/2016-01-on-spiritual-gluttony-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jan 2016 22:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2016/01/16/2016-01-on-spiritual-gluttony-html/</guid>
      <description>In Dark Night of the Soul, St. John of the Cross exposes a host of attitudes and behaviors we may not realize are sins, as they are borne out of spiritual practices. The one that grabbed my attention today was “spiritual gluttony”. This is where we crave and pursue the sweetness of spiritual mountain-top experiences more than we do our Savior.
It was hitting so close to home that I thought maybe I was misreading it &amp;#8211; putting my own thoughts into the 16-century monk’s head.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Countdown</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2016/01/07/2016-01-the-countdown-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2016 22:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2016/01/07/2016-01-the-countdown-html/</guid>
      <description>In less than 48 hours, I will be entering a modified Daniel Fast. There is nothing magical about this type of fast; I think it’s just more accessible for many of us. Because I’m still breastfeeding twin boys several times a day, I’m not going to complicate my life by changing this family’s entire diet for 10 days. That would inevitably turn the fast itself into an idol, as I’d scurry about the kitchen picking my brain and the mass brain of the internet for recipes and nutritional considerations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>From the other side of the chrysalis</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2015/12/11/2015-12-from-other-side-of-chrysalis-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2015 16:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2015/12/11/2015-12-from-other-side-of-chrysalis-html/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;#8217;ve had a few weeks to process the dissolution of our weekly Milkweed Momdays. This past Monday was the first without the Bible study written on my calendar. (To be more accurate, it was written on the calendar, but I crossed it off.)
Through reflections both in solitude and in the safe exploration afforded by the presence of gentle and wise friends, my perspective is widening beyond the sacrifice of my &amp;#8220;baby&amp;#8221; on that mountain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unsent</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2015/12/03/2015-12-letter-to-my-departed-friend-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2015 15:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2015/12/03/2015-12-letter-to-my-departed-friend-html/</guid>
      <description>Dear Shawn,
It has been exactly 10 years since we met. If you hadn&amp;#8217;t left this earth that day in July, I wouldn&amp;#8217;t have realized this. I also wouldn&amp;#8217;t find myself tearing up at thoughts of eating toast at a family restaurant, or searching intensely through my CD collection for that scratched-up disc with &amp;#8220;Trudy&amp;#8221; scrawled on it which we found in a parking lot, deciding I absolutely must keep it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cocoons</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2015/11/22/2015-11-cocoons-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2015 19:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2015/11/22/2015-11-cocoons-html/</guid>
      <description>On November 1 of this year, I wrote in my journal, &amp;#8220;I feel like something is about to turn.&amp;#8221;
The next day, we met for our weekly Milkweed Momday and launched one of our own monarch butterflies, a mama named Jamie, out of our milkweed and into her new adventure.
&amp;#8220;How exciting,&amp;#8221; I mused to my Shepherd. &amp;#8220;Now, what&amp;#8217;s next?&amp;#8221;
I felt Him inviting me up a mountain. It looked like a beautiful hike.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Holes in Wood</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2015/11/08/2015-11-holes-in-wood-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Nov 2015 21:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2015/11/08/2015-11-holes-in-wood-html/</guid>
      <description>There is a popular anecdote about a kid with anger issues. Here&amp;#8217;s a version of it:
&amp;#8220;&amp;#8216;There once was a little boy who had a bad temper. His father gave him a bag of nails and told him that every time he lost his temper, he must hammer a nail into the back of the fence.&amp;nbsp;
The first day the boy had&amp;nbsp; driven 37 nails into the fence. Over the next few weeks, as he learned to control his anger, the number of nails hammered daily gradually dwindled down.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trajectory</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2015/11/05/2015-11-trajectory-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2015 23:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2015/11/05/2015-11-trajectory-html/</guid>
      <description>The videos I store in my head seem to be cataloged into three categories:
 Life-changing moments
 Non-life-changing moments that still made an impact for some reason
 Things that pop up from time to time which I&amp;#8217;ve forgotten about until God has some reason to remind me of them
  On my anniversary, I&amp;#8217;m playing the memory of standing on that playground in October 2007, shivering with friends and family from the damp coolness as my fiance slides a ring onto my finger.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Toeing the line</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2015/11/01/2015-11-toeing-line-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2015 23:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2015/11/01/2015-11-toeing-line-html/</guid>
      <description>I don&amp;#8217;t know many people who are great at hearing the word, &amp;#8220;No.&amp;#8221;
In fact, as I typed that statement, I attempted to tally up everyone in my mental Rolodex who could graciously accept a negative response, and no one popped up. There has to be at least one person I know who is gifted in that area; I just don&amp;#8217;t have them on speed-dial for it.
And as I typed that last paragraph, I realized there is a large portion of the population who would not know what I was talking about when I referenced &amp;#8220;Rolodex&amp;#8221; and &amp;#8220;speed-dial&amp;#8221;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fits and starts</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2015/10/29/2015-10-fits-and-starts-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2015 03:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2015/10/29/2015-10-fits-and-starts-html/</guid>
      <description>I am no stranger to inconsistency. I know how to start a project with passion and drive&amp;#8230;and never finish it. I have a spotty history of coming and going in friendships and commitments. And, as a native Detroiter, I have weathered the vacillating reputations of the Pistons and the Tigers (although the Lions have been fairly consistent through the years).
And then something happened.
Namely, The Message version of Ephesians 4:2:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Burnt Out on Burnout</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2015/10/24/2015-10-burnt-out-on-burnout-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2015 02:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2015/10/24/2015-10-burnt-out-on-burnout-html/</guid>
      <description>There has been a common underlying theme in several of my conversations recently. I think the title of this post gave it away &amp;#8211; maybe I should have been a bit more sneaky and teased the story better. Next time.
As I was contemplating how prevalent burnout is among women who love to serve in ministry, who are sooooo ready to use their gifts, I realized what a marvelous scam it is for the enemy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digesting with gratitude</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2015/09/30/2015-09-digesting-with-gratitude-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2015 18:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2015/09/30/2015-09-digesting-with-gratitude-html/</guid>
      <description>Dear patrons of the local Mexican restaurant my family frequents,
Thank you for allowing my husband and me to argue in your midst. Thank you for averting your eyes and not [audibly] questioning our decision to hash it all out in front of our young children. This has been a long journey for us to get to this place in our marriage, where we can be real with each other and show our disagreements instead of forced pleasantries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Of Lemons and Lost Paychecks</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2015/09/23/2015-09-of-lemons-and-lost-paychecks-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2015 02:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2015/09/23/2015-09-of-lemons-and-lost-paychecks-html/</guid>
      <description>Before the onset of children, my husband sold his reliable red 2003 Ford Focus ZX5 so he could get something bigger, more adult-looking, with more trunk space. He wanted to be able to haul our film equipment more easily, and there were only so many Tetris moves he could do to fit it all in the little hatchback.
And so, of course, we ended up with a bright yellow 2003 Mini Cooper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>From a mom of 3 under 4 to the incoming grad school student</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2015/09/20/2015-09-from-mom-of-3-under-4-to-fff-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2015 00:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2015/09/20/2015-09-from-mom-of-3-under-4-to-fff-html/</guid>
      <description>Below is a letter I posted at my new blog, Verses 3 to 5, where Christian women can post letters to their former selves. God&amp;#8217;s grace is so good!
Dear 22-year-old Jessy,
First of all, I know how closed you are to advice, especially any that comes from someone who approaches you with an attitude of, &amp;#8220;I&amp;#8217;m older, so I know.&amp;#8221; It seems condescending, and I will strive to avoid that here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Inclusive Misfit</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2015/09/12/2015-09-the-inclusive-misfit-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2015 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2015/09/12/2015-09-the-inclusive-misfit-html/</guid>
      <description>This morning, I watched my firstborn swallow her animated boldness to don the ill-tailored costume of a timid wallflower. It was her first tumbling class, and she was the youngest kiddo, the only new student, and therefore did not yet have a self-selected buddy. She hung back as the more experienced students ran, hopped, and jumping-jacked their way around the small dance studio. And I felt every one of her feelings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corrosion</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2015/04/01/2015-04-corrosion-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2015 18:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2015/04/01/2015-04-corrosion-html/</guid>
      <description>As I&amp;#8217;ve spent time in authentic community &amp;#8211; something I avoided for years out of fear of being known &amp;#8211; I have started to see how the Spirit has re-sensitized me. Or perhaps there is no &amp;#8220;re-&amp;#8220;; perhaps it&amp;#8217;s for the first time.
For example, today I experienced a frustration, and I thought through a careful reaction &amp;amp; implemented it. But I still felt lousy about it, despite the tactfulness I was so fastidious to apply.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eating Hands</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2015/03/31/2015-03-eating-hands-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2015 04:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2015/03/31/2015-03-eating-hands-html/</guid>
      <description>My kiddos are adorable, but not brilliant. At least, not yet. When I go to nurse their hungry little 4-month-old mouths, I often find they have preemptively shoved a fist into it. In an effort to sate their appetite, they find something that works in a tactile way but not nutritionally.
If only they knew to wait! That their mama is equipped and happy to provide them with what they need to thrive!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Should You Stay or Should You Go?</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2015/03/19/2015-03-should-you-stay-or-should-you-go-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2015 23:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2015/03/19/2015-03-should-you-stay-or-should-you-go-html/</guid>
      <description>Okay, this one may hurt. Loving Daddy, let any wounds that result be trusted as those of a friend (Proverbs 27:6) &amp;amp; as those of Your truth.
Earlier this year, we were discussing in Milkweed our theme verse/passage for 2015. Mine is justice, specifically as it relates to the &amp;#8220;fast&amp;#8221; described in Isaiah 58:6-12. As I&amp;#8217;ve been meditating on this, the Spirit has been redefining my perception of oppression &amp;amp; justice: It&amp;#8217;s not just about slavery, the homeless, minorities, &amp;amp; other headlines in the news, although all of those require us to take action &amp;amp; show love.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Power of Relaxing</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2015/03/01/2015-02-the-power-of-relaxing-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2015 01:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2015/03/01/2015-02-the-power-of-relaxing-html/</guid>
      <description>So I was driving home this evening from taking my 3 sick kiddos &amp;amp; under-the-weather self to see my dad off to his flight back to Hungary, and I heard an interview with DJ Dan Deacon. In honor of the end of this week of rest in Milkweed, read this excerpt &amp;amp; prepare to have your brain shifted a bit!
&amp;#8220;I was doing what I thought was relaxing, but was actually just killing time: I was on Facebook.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Consequences of Cleansing</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2015/02/13/2015-02-the-consequences-of-cleansing-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2015 01:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2015/02/13/2015-02-the-consequences-of-cleansing-html/</guid>
      <description>God loves object lessons. Just look at the Old Testament prophets &amp;amp; how He had them deliver important messages to kings! So here&amp;#8217;s what He taught me last night. Does this make me royalty?
Bob &amp;amp; I had a much-needed date night last night (with the boys), so we went to an inexpensive family restaurant with his birthday money &amp;amp; pigged out. I ate portions &amp;amp; food I haven&amp;#8217;t had in years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pushing Together or Pulling Apart</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2014/12/28/2014-12-pushing-together-or-pulling-apart-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2014 01:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2014/12/28/2014-12-pushing-together-or-pulling-apart-html/</guid>
      <description>One of the great things in life is how we change &amp;amp; our interests evolve. This can be great for our marriages&amp;#8230;or it can pull you apart if you don&amp;#8217;t work to include one another in those developments. It&amp;#8217;s so easy to believe the lie, &amp;#8220;We just aren&amp;#8217;t compatible anymore,&amp;#8221; but that doesn&amp;#8217;t jive with God&amp;#8217;s definition of marriage. Growth in us can bring growth in our relationships when we don&amp;#8217;t just focus on ourselves!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Redeemed Parenting</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2014/12/27/2014-12-redeemed-parenting-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2014 01:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2014/12/27/2014-12-redeemed-parenting-html/</guid>
      <description>When you come from a background where your parents&amp;#8217; parenting was ineffective (or worse), it can be a real worry that you will repeat their legacy. The great news is that when we have an active, grace-filled relationship with our loving Daddy, He enters in &amp;amp; rewrites the story! But we desperately need to be in community, humbly listening to others &amp;amp; accepting wisdom where we are lacking. This doesn&amp;#8217;t mean we take every piece of unsolicited advice that comes our way, but rather we use discernment to recognize that God brings us together as a Body to raise His precious little ones!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to the World</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2014/12/01/2014-12-welcome-to-world-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2014 18:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2014/12/01/2014-12-welcome-to-world-html/</guid>
      <description>On a personal note, I had twins yesterday. The two boys join their daddy &amp;amp; sister in our wacky home. Off to cocoon for a few hours &amp;amp; bask in this double joy&amp;#8230;
~A woman giving birth to a child has pain because her time has come; but when her baby is born she forgets the anguish because of her joy that a child is born into the world.~
John 16:21</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CAST</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/project/cast/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2014 02:13:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/project/cast/</guid>
      <description>About project Aenean ipsum justo, semper eu nisl ut, pretium tincidunt sem. Praesent et diam sit amet lacus lobortis dictum a id lacus. Quisque hendrerit sit amet turpis eu varius. Ut id lorem ac felis ultrices tincidunt. Pellentesque consequat arcu ac fringilla imperdiet. Phasellus pellentesque, sapien non pulvinar blandit, sapien ante aliquet felis, vel porttitor sapien ante in lacus. Fusce non urna aliquet, malesuada nibh vel, luctus urna. Phasellus ut lacus molestie, varius purus quis, malesuada lorem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Raising Unicorns</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/project/raising-unicorns/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2014 02:13:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/project/raising-unicorns/</guid>
      <description>Aenean ipsum justo, semper eu nisl ut, pretium tincidunt sem. Praesent et diam sit amet lacus lobortis dictum a id lacus. Quisque hendrerit sit amet turpis eu varius. Ut id lorem ac felis ultrices tincidunt. Pellentesque consequat arcu ac fringilla imperdiet. Phasellus pellentesque, sapien non pulvinar blandit, sapien ante aliquet felis, vel porttitor sapien ante in lacus. Fusce non urna aliquet, malesuada nibh vel, luctus urna. Phasellus ut lacus molestie, varius purus quis, malesuada lorem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Verses 3 to 5</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/project/verses3to5/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2014 02:13:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/project/verses3to5/</guid>
      <description>Aenean ipsum justo, semper eu nisl ut, pretium tincidunt sem. Praesent et diam sit amet lacus lobortis dictum a id lacus. Quisque hendrerit sit amet turpis eu varius. Ut id lorem ac felis ultrices tincidunt. Pellentesque consequat arcu ac fringilla imperdiet. Phasellus pellentesque, sapien non pulvinar blandit, sapien ante aliquet felis, vel porttitor sapien ante in lacus. Fusce non urna aliquet, malesuada nibh vel, luctus urna. Phasellus ut lacus molestie, varius purus quis, malesuada lorem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Milkweed Turns 1 Year Old, Isn’t Moldy Yet</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2014/11/15/2014-11-milkweed-turns-1-year-old-isnt-moldy-yet-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2014 01:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2014/11/15/2014-11-milkweed-turns-1-year-old-isnt-moldy-yet-html/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;#8217;s hard to believe my Milkweed family of mamas has been meeting online &amp;amp; in person for over a year! What a tremendous community our loving Daddy has brought together here to pray, encourage, laugh, challenge, &amp;amp; grow.
Some have asked how this group started, and I thought I&amp;#8217;d be a bit transparent here. Last year, my marriage was going through some really hard stuff. I was desperate for other ladies to pray with me, lift me up, hold me accountable, speak truth to me, but I realized how spiritually isolated I had become as a stay-at-home mama.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sharing Victories</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2014/11/03/2014-11-sharing-victories-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2014 01:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2014/11/03/2014-11-sharing-victories-html/</guid>
      <description>Lately, God has been speaking to me a lot about redemption. What a sweet word that is! What awesomeness to contemplate! Our loving Daddy grinds up all our poop into manure that grows beauty &amp;amp; life!&amp;nbsp;
We must share regularly with each other &amp;amp; with our kiddos about how God has redeemed us, all His mighty works in our own lives. Psalm 78:5-8 talks about how these reminders will keep our children from becoming rebellious against God.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Freedom from Mommy Guilt</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2014/10/24/2014-10-as-women-as-moms-were-subtly-fed-lies-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2014 00:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2014/10/24/2014-10-as-women-as-moms-were-subtly-fed-lies-html/</guid>
      <description>As women &amp;#8211; as moms &amp;#8211; we&amp;#8217;re subtly fed the lies that we should always carry some degree of guilt &amp;amp; an endearing tendency toward worry. It&amp;#8217;s almost like a membership card or a badge of honor.
Here&amp;#8217;s the crazy part: Jesus died to set us free from all that! It breaks His heart when we choose to cling to shame, anxiety, &amp;amp; regret. He wants us to choose life &amp;amp; the freedom that cost Him so much.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grudge Removal</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2014/10/12/2014-10-grudge-removal-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2014 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2014/10/12/2014-10-grudge-removal-html/</guid>
      <description>~I urge Euodia and Syntyche to iron out their differences and make up. God doesn’t want his children holding grudges. And, oh, yes, Syzygus, since you’re right there to help them work things out, do your best with them. These women worked for the Message hand in hand with Clement and me, and with the other veterans—worked as hard as any of us. Remember, their names are also in the Book of Life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dethroning Money</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2014/10/06/2014-10-dethroning-money-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2014 00:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2014/10/06/2014-10-dethroning-money-html/</guid>
      <description>Please take a moment to STOP, READ, &amp;amp; PRAY on the following statement. It applies to so many of us. Our Savior can &amp;amp; wants to free us all in this way! Thank You, loving Daddy. Guide us out of our shackles.
~When Christ redeemed you, He forgave your moral indebtedness and your wrongdoing. You were spiritually reconciled to God&amp;#8230; But if you haven&amp;#8217;t received a second reconciliation &amp;#8211; a financial reconciliation in which the power of God breaks the power of money in your life, His love cleanses your shame and guilt about your financial state, and the Holy Spirit fills you with the power to move ahead with all-new financial practices &amp;#8211; well, friend, in my opinion, you&amp;#8217;re still one reconciliation short.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flame Retardants Need Not Apply</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2014/10/03/2014-10-flame-retardants-need-not-apply-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2014 00:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2014/10/03/2014-10-flame-retardants-need-not-apply-html/</guid>
      <description>~Don’t burn out; keep yourselves fueled and aflame. Be alert servants of the Master, cheerfully expectant. Don’t quit in hard times; pray all the harder. Help needy Christians; be inventive in hospitality.~
Romans 12:11-13
What does all this point to? Regular rest, self-care, &amp;amp; quiet time in the King&amp;#8217;s presence. If you aren&amp;#8217;t making time for these, humbly cry out to Daddy, the Creator of time, and He will guide you into R&amp;amp;R so you can truly worship &amp;amp; serve with a fresh filling of the Spirit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It’s Okay to Be Happy</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2014/10/01/2014-09-its-okay-to-be-happy-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2014 00:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2014/10/01/2014-09-its-okay-to-be-happy-html/</guid>
      <description>When someone you know is sad, suffering, or searching and God has gifted you with a season of abundance, it can feel wrong to celebrate it &amp;amp; feel joy. Romans 12:15 tells us to &amp;#8220;weep with those who weep,&amp;#8221; after all.
However, it also says to &amp;#8220;rejoice with those who rejoice&amp;#8221; &amp;#8211; and He wants that to be you! Your grieving friends &amp;#8211; if they are of sound mind &amp;amp; heart &amp;#8211; do not want you to miss out on enjoying the blessings Daddy designed &amp;amp; delivered to you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We Are More Than Just The Givers Of Life To Our Children</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2014/09/30/2014-09-we-are-more-than-just-givers-of-life-to-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2014 00:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2014/09/30/2014-09-we-are-more-than-just-givers-of-life-to-html/</guid>
      <description>We are more than just the givers of life to our children. We form their templates of who women are &amp;amp; how they should act &amp;#8211; &amp;amp; demand to be treated. We introduce them to the beginning of their values, worldview, &amp;amp; the authenticity of what we claim to believe.
Be in consistent community &amp;#8211; church, Bible study, Christian friendships, etc &amp;#8211; that supports what you want to instill. I grew up with fairly healthy messages about Jesus &amp;amp; Christian living in my home, but the summer Bible camps &amp;amp; youth group I attended were more conservative &amp;amp; legalistic &amp;amp; sent a lot of damaging messages I&amp;#8217;ve had to learn to undo by God&amp;#8217;s grace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temptation Is…</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2014/09/19/2014-09-temptation-is-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2014 00:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2014/09/19/2014-09-temptation-is-html/</guid>
      <description>Temptation doesn&amp;#8217;t just mean lust. For some of us, the temptation is to react in anger, judge others, please others, or overeat; for others, the temptation is to get bogged down by our past or give in to anxiety about our future.
Temptation will affect us all &amp;#8211; especially when we&amp;#8217;re striving to obey our loving Daddy. The temptation is not sin; the response to it can be. The great news is our All-Powerful Defender gives us the power to resist temptation!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5-Minute Reflection</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2014/09/16/2014-09-5-minute-reflection-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2014 00:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2014/09/16/2014-09-5-minute-reflection-html/</guid>
      <description>Take 5 minutes at the end of each day to record the following from that day:
 3 things you&amp;#8217;re grateful for 1 thing that touched you 1 thing that inspired you 1 thing that challenged you  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sabbath as a Preemptive Strike</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2014/09/07/2014-09-sabbath-as-preemptive-strike-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2014 00:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2014/09/07/2014-09-sabbath-as-preemptive-strike-html/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;#8217;m just starting to get that God gave us Sabbath rest not as a rule but as a blessing. He knows the frailty &amp;amp; limitations of our human bodies, and He lovingly has given us a proactive guideline to keep us from becoming our own worst enemies! Take that, burn-out!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Everyone Needs in Their Medicine Cabinet</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2014/08/31/2014-08-what-everyone-needs-in-their-medicine-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2014 00:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2014/08/31/2014-08-what-everyone-needs-in-their-medicine-html/</guid>
      <description>Last night, I had a pretty scary reaction due to a medication/pregnancy hormone interaction, and it threw one more grievance on top of my massive pile of maternity issues. But what I&amp;#8217;ve found to be most effective in combating the vacuum of self-pity isn&amp;#8217;t Tylenol or ginger essential oil or urgent calls to my midwife. It&amp;#8217;s gratitude. It&amp;#8217;s trust my loving Daddy is sovereign &amp;amp; is always with me &amp;amp; using this all to His glory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When Your Sin Isn’t Cool Enough</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2014/08/29/2014-08-when-your-sin-isnt-cool-enough-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2014 00:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2014/08/29/2014-08-when-your-sin-isnt-cool-enough-html/</guid>
      <description>As inspiring as it is to hear about God&amp;#8217;s forgiveness toward drug addicts &amp;amp; murderers, how atheists can do a 180 &amp;amp; serial adulterers can experience fulfillment in the redemptive love of Jesus, these stories can also isolate us. They can make us think, &amp;#8220;I&amp;#8217;m not that bad &amp;#8211; why would God waste His massive, precious grace on someone who just cheats a bit on her taxes or had sex with her boyfriend in high school or secretly judges others for their parenting styles?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Incomplete Intro to Fasting</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2014/08/27/2014-08-an-incomplete-intro-to-fasting-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2014 00:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2014/08/27/2014-08-an-incomplete-intro-to-fasting-html/</guid>
      <description>Fasting. There, I said it.
A lot of you are facing some difficult, even impossible, situations. Prayer is essential! And I also want to encourage you to consider fasting to allow the Spirit greater access to break down those extra-stubborn strongholds of the enemy.
Maybe you can&amp;#8217;t do a day of fasting from food, but you can forgo one meal &amp;amp; use those hunger pains to remind you of your dependence on the Redeemer &amp;amp; Healer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Being the Chosen One</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2014/08/24/2014-08-being-chosen-one-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2014 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2014/08/24/2014-08-being-chosen-one-html/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;#8217;m about to get a big sci-fi-geeky here, but bear with me because I think you&amp;#8217;ll be encouraged by the end.
I&amp;#8217;ve been reading Bill Hybels&amp;#8217; call-to-passion book Holy Discontent, and I realized how we all kinda want to be Luke Skywalker, Harry Potter, Queen Esther, Sydney Bristow in Alias, Bethany Sloane in Dogma, and all those other &amp;#8220;chosen ones&amp;#8221;. As audience members, we relate with these characters because we rather like the idea of having ancient writings foretell our coming, or other people recognize us as the person who will accomplish what needs to be done.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wasted Words</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2014/08/22/2014-08-wasted-words-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2014 01:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2014/08/22/2014-08-wasted-words-html/</guid>
      <description>As women, so many of us enjoy sharing our life stories &amp;amp; advice we have learned with people we think need it. However, this isn&amp;#8217;t always helpful &amp;#8211; if we were honest with ourselves, all too often we share for ourselves &amp;amp; not to truly benefit the hearer. This act of non-listening can create distance between ourselves &amp;amp; others&amp;#8230;and those &amp;#8220;others&amp;#8221; may be our children or husbands. Let&amp;#8217;s all ask the Spirit for guidance next time we have an urge to speak into another&amp;#8217;s life, so that our words are life-giving &amp;amp; blessed by God!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Purposeful Parenting</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2014/08/18/2014-08-purposeful-parenting-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2014 01:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2014/08/18/2014-08-purposeful-parenting-html/</guid>
      <description>We are our children&amp;#8217;s first understanding of God as a loving Parent. When we look on our children lovingly, wisely, &amp;amp; attentively, they can begin to fathom there is a Divine Being who does the same!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Banishing the Bad Moms</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2014/07/30/2014-07-banishing-bad-moms-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 01:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2014/07/30/2014-07-banishing-bad-moms-html/</guid>
      <description>If you find yourself saying, &amp;#8220;I&amp;#8217;m a bad mom,&amp;#8221; or even thinking it, those words are not from God. He doesn&amp;#8217;t label us &amp;amp; send us off to pasture; He loves us where we are &amp;amp; helps us grow from there. He is a loving Daddy who wants us to serve Him in our work &amp;amp; take pleasure in it!
Would you want your child to build a tower then declare, &amp;#8220;I&amp;#8217;m a terrible builder!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with WHIMSY (or Me on Film)</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2014/06/02/2014-06-working-with-whimsy-or-me-on-film-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2014 04:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2014/06/02/2014-06-working-with-whimsy-or-me-on-film-html/</guid>
      <description>I had the incredible opportunity to present on my book, Raising Unicorns, in Berlin last month at the re:publica conference. I talked about the importance of WHIMSY. Enjoy, my friends!
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thinking Straight</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2014/04/22/2014-04-thinking-straight-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2014 01:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2014/04/22/2014-04-thinking-straight-html/</guid>
      <description>When it feels like your thoughts are out of control or like they&amp;#8217;re controlling you, starting praising God. Say, &amp;#8220;Jesus, You are my Savior. Daddy, I belong to you. You are my King!&amp;#8221; Sing from your heart, clap your hands &amp;#8211; worship like your mind depends on it, because it does! You&amp;#8217;ll be amazed at the clarity you receive when you turn to praise instead of letting your thoughts drag you down.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Affection Reflection</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2014/04/16/2014-04-affection-reflection-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2014 01:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2014/04/16/2014-04-affection-reflection-html/</guid>
      <description>We brag about our kiddos because we spend so much time with them, feeling their love, enjoying their uniqueness. This is what happens when we genuinely engage. If our words &amp;amp; attitudes don&amp;#8217;t reflect this kind of affection for our loving Daddy, it&amp;#8217;s time for us to take some dedicated time alone to genuinely engage with Him! So listen to the birds, read a Psalm, and bask in His gentle &amp;amp; unconditional grace today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Lie of Guilt</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2014/04/03/2014-04-the-lie-of-guilt-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2014 01:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2014/04/03/2014-04-the-lie-of-guilt-html/</guid>
      <description>A great tragedy is that guilt has become associated with God. Not only is this not one of His choice tools, it&amp;#8217;s not one of His tools at all! When the Spirit convicts our hearts, the message is not a harsh, &amp;#8220;Get this right and then we&amp;#8217;ll talk,&amp;#8221; but a gentle, &amp;#8220;Hey, see that thing over there? Would you please give it to Me? It&amp;#8217;s getting in the way of us being closer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sacred Setbacks</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2014/03/30/2014-03-sacred-setbacks-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2014 01:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2014/03/30/2014-03-sacred-setbacks-html/</guid>
      <description>Life is never a smooth, steady, upward climb toward our own goals. In His wisdom, our loving Daddy interjects other plans, pathways, &amp;amp; lessons for us so we can become the beloved servants He designed each of us to be.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rescue</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2014/03/12/2014-03-rescue-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2014 01:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2014/03/12/2014-03-rescue-html/</guid>
      <description>God is our Rescuer. That doesn&amp;#8217;t mean His rescue will come right away &amp;#8211; it depends on what He wants to accomplish in your life through your current trial. Still, He will always protect you from what will destroy that which He plans to accomplish in &amp;amp; through you. He will be your Refuge, He will be right by your side, when you call on Him. (Psalm 91:14-15)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Just As I Am</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2014/03/06/2014-03-just-as-i-am-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2014 02:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2014/03/06/2014-03-just-as-i-am-html/</guid>
      <description>It seems whenever I start an attempt to better myself, I run into the situation Lisa Simpson encounters in a famous Simpsons episode about pursuing vegan living: There is always a level of commitment higher than my current one.
I want to eat healthier, then discover the all-natural chicken I picked up is not organic. And then the organic chicken I bought was not free-range. And then that free-range chicken in my fridge was not locally raised.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Walls &amp; Focus</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2014/02/27/2014-02-walls-focus-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2014 02:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2014/02/27/2014-02-walls-focus-html/</guid>
      <description>Do you feel a wall in your heart? God knows it&amp;#8217;s there, and He wants to remove it. He wants our hearts to be soft, malleable, &amp;amp; open to His Spirit&amp;#8217;s movement within. Be honest with Him about its presence, and let Him show you how it got there so He can dismantle it &amp;#8211; brick by brick or with a mighty explosion, depending on what He wants you to learn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Diet</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2014/02/05/2014-02-new-diet-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2014 02:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2014/02/05/2014-02-new-diet-html/</guid>
      <description>Eliminate cynicism  Reduce sarcasm Detoxify your life of any toxic relationships Load up on Jesus&amp;#8217; love, hope, &amp;amp; truth, as well as authentic God-lovin&amp;#8217; community.&amp;nbsp;   You&amp;#8217;ll feel pounds lighter &amp;amp; years younger. (1 Peter 5:7)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In Praise of Dedicated Mamas</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2014/01/17/2014-01-in-praise-of-dedicated-mamas-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2014 03:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2014/01/17/2014-01-in-praise-of-dedicated-mamas-html/</guid>
      <description>The radio has a growing catalog of songs about girls&amp;#8217; low self-esteem. From One Direction&amp;#8217;s &amp;#8220;You Don&amp;#8217;t Know You&amp;#8217;re Beautiful&amp;#8221; to &amp;#8220;You Are More&amp;#8221; by Tenth Avenue North, from TLC&amp;#8217;s &amp;#8220;UnPretty&amp;#8221; to &amp;#8220;More Beautiful You&amp;#8221; by Jonny Diaz, our young ladies &amp;amp; our young selves &amp;amp; even our current selves struggle with our worth. Ladies don&amp;#8217;t own their beauty; they look great but feel lousy. And that is where mamas come in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stocking Stuffer</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2013/12/05/2013-12-stocking-stuffer-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2013 03:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2013/12/05/2013-12-stocking-stuffer-html/</guid>
      <description>Are you struggling with peace, joy, &amp;amp; gratitude this Christmas season?
DO: Immerse yourself in our loving Daddy&amp;#8217;s Word &amp;#8211; especially the Psalms.
DON&amp;#8217;T: Watch sappy rom-com holiday movies that induce a bad case of the &amp;#8220;If-only&amp;#8217;s&amp;#8221;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Giving Thanks When Your Heart Hurts</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2013/11/29/2013-11-giving-thanks-when-your-heart-hurts-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2013 03:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2013/11/29/2013-11-giving-thanks-when-your-heart-hurts-html/</guid>
      <description>Today may not be the happiest Thanksgiving for some of us, and our loving Daddy knows that. So let&amp;#8217;s challenge ourselves today to be grateful &amp;amp; give praise in the midst of our current trials, trusting Him that next year&amp;#8217;s Thanksgiving might just be spent in gratitude for what He brought out of this season.
~His purpose for our trials is often to bring us humbly before Him to experience a breaking in our inner, independent, self-sufficient selves, and grow us up into compassionate, patient, spiritually strong, God-glorifying people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boundaries: A Primer</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2013/11/23/2013-11-boundaries-primer-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2013 03:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2013/11/23/2013-11-boundaries-primer-html/</guid>
      <description>Setting boundaries probably won&amp;#8217;t feel great at first, and the other person probably won&amp;#8217;t like them. And that is exactly why we need to trust the Spirit to give us discernment &amp;amp; strength, and surround ourselves with healthy people who will keep us on our path to wholeness! (Proverbs 13:20, Hebrews 10:25)
So, how do you set them? Boundaries can be reactive: &amp;#8220;You&amp;#8217;ve crossed the line, now back off!&amp;#8221; But to be healthy &amp;amp; live God&amp;#8217;s love, we need to move to proactive boundaries: &amp;#8220;Here&amp;#8217;s where the line is, so I&amp;#8217;ll give you a friendly heads-up when you&amp;#8217;re within 50 feet of it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Unnecessary Cover-Up</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2013/11/11/2013-11-an-unnecessary-cover-up-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2013 03:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2013/11/11/2013-11-an-unnecessary-cover-up-html/</guid>
      <description>The painting in the gallery window clearly had a mistake made in it early on that the artist had tried very hard to cover up. With all her effort, though, it was still evident. Had the mistake been corrected at the start, it would have looked flawless &amp;amp; been less work in the long run.
So it is with training up our kiddos. Let&amp;#8217;s learn how to lay the groundwork first with God&amp;#8217;s help, correcting mistakes from the start instead of covering them up until they become even more obvious!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wise Prepping</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2013/11/08/2013-11-wise-prepping-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2013 03:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2013/11/08/2013-11-wise-prepping-html/</guid>
      <description>Need to have a difficult conversation today? Talk to God first! He&amp;#8217;ll give you the words, timing, and wisdom you require &amp;#8211; and His Spirit can do some prep work in the other person.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#43;/-</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2013/11/06/2013-11-blog-post-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2013 03:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2013/11/06/2013-11-blog-post-html/</guid>
      <description>Our words are like pluses and minuses to those to whom we speak, and the minuses can often take away more than the pluses give. Let&amp;#8217;s be intentional, then, to speak pluses &amp;#8211; to speak life. Let&amp;#8217;s give the Holy Spirit control of our words today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rest, Again.</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2013/10/26/2013-10-rest-again-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2013 02:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2013/10/26/2013-10-rest-again-html/</guid>
      <description>If God is your ultimate Boss, what are His expectations of you? To work wholeheartedly and to rest. These depend on one another other &amp;#8211; you can&amp;#8217;t truly enjoy one without the other!
(Colossians 3:23-24, Matthew 11:29)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>rest</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2013/10/23/2013-10-rest-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2013 02:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2013/10/23/2013-10-rest-html/</guid>
      <description>have you rested today? even if it&amp;#8217;s only for 3 minutes, do it with your whole heart for those 3 minutes. it honors God!&amp;nbsp; (colossians 3:23) plus, when we intentionally create space in our days to rest, God can use that space to take us deeper &amp;amp; give us His limitless peace. it&amp;#8217;s like making a deposit in a savings account with 1000% rates!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Milkweed &#43; Cottonwood = I’m Back!</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2013/10/10/2013-10-milkweed-cottonwood-im-back-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2013 02:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2013/10/10/2013-10-milkweed-cottonwood-im-back-html/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;#8217;s been a while, my friends! I&amp;#8217;ve taken a few years off to quit my job, have a kid, write a book entitled Raising Unicorns, and start a Bible study for mamas of young kiddos called Milkweed. It&amp;#8217;s been an amazing time of transition, and this season has brought about a slew of new insights into God&amp;#8217;s love &amp;amp; grace. As a friend once shared with me:
If you want to experience God, stay single.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harmony vs. Melody</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2013/03/28/2013-03-harmony-vs-melody-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2013 02:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2013/03/28/2013-03-harmony-vs-melody-html/</guid>
      <description>Harmony isn&amp;#8217;t the same as melody. Melody is a homogenous tone; harmony is a blending of differences that produce a fuller sound. This Thanksgiving, let&amp;#8217;s be thankful for the harmony in our lives &amp;#8211; &amp;amp; pursue even more! (Romans 12:16)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>day #94</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2010/04/14/2010-04-day-94-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Apr 2010 14:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2010/04/14/2010-04-day-94-html/</guid>
      <description>coming out from under a dark cloud.
my passion has been tested &amp;amp; refined during the past few months,
and i&amp;#8217;m happy to say that i&amp;#8217;m starting to see it again.
and this time, it&amp;#8217;s version 2.0!
i&amp;#8217;ve come to recognize that my core values &amp;amp; strengths were not aligned with my behavior.
my energy was being diffused by activities &amp;amp; investments that were incongruent.
so i&amp;#8217;ve taken some time to reacquaint myself with my &amp;#8220;core&amp;#8221;,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>day #69</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2010/03/10/2010-03-day-69-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2010 14:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2010/03/10/2010-03-day-69-html/</guid>
      <description>spent last weekend in a screenwriting workshop.
this is a passion i&amp;#8217;ve put off for a while.
i&amp;#8217;ve dabbled here &amp;amp; there,
but i wouldn&amp;#8217;t allow myself to dive in.
with bob&amp;#8217;s encouragement, i did it.
it was a huge time &amp;amp; $ commitment,
but it was worth it.
i stretched.
i was uncomfortable.
i was creative.
and now there is no turning back.
to have that kind of opportunity &amp;amp; not do anything with it is ungrateful &amp;amp; unwise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>day #55</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2010/02/24/2010-02-day-55-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2010 14:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2010/02/24/2010-02-day-55-html/</guid>
      <description>~be cheerful no matter what; pray all the time; thank God no matter what happens.~
1 thessalonians 5:16-18
it&amp;#8217;s been a busy/tough past 2 weeks,
at least 4 days of which were spent sprawled on the couch in pain from a toothache.
but there was still joy in the pain, and passion to be celebrated.
the thing i&amp;#8217;m learning this month about passion is that it comes from unexpected places &amp;amp; at unexpected times.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>day #43</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2010/02/12/2010-02-day-43-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2010 15:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2010/02/12/2010-02-day-43-html/</guid>
      <description>been reading through 1 thessalonians, &amp;amp; skipping over parts.
this is amusing to me, as the book is only 4 pages long in the message bible.
however, i found i couldn&amp;#8217;t relate with some elements &amp;amp; moved on.
and then i took a moment this morning to ask myself:
why can&amp;#8217;t i relate?
what are those elements?
the answer was this:
i couldn&amp;#8217;t relate with the intensity of love that paul expressed toward the thessalonians.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>day #41</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2010/02/11/2010-02-day-41-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2010 01:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2010/02/11/2010-02-day-41-html/</guid>
      <description>it&amp;#8217;s a birthday party!
i&amp;#8217;ve been tied up with work, school, &amp;amp; a sick cat,
and today is bob&amp;#8217;s birthday.
but i&amp;#8217;ve managed to make time &amp;amp; create space to embrace this special day.
birthdays are an interesting phenomenon.
they&amp;#8217;re a celebration of life &amp;amp; the uniqueness of each person,
but they can also be times of stress &amp;amp; the unpleasantry of unmet expectations.
today, i&amp;#8217;m going easy on myself &amp;amp; bob so we can truly enjoy his day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>days #31-39</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2010/02/08/2010-02-days-31-39-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2010 15:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2010/02/08/2010-02-days-31-39-html/</guid>
      <description>it&amp;#8217;s been a long, hard week.
lots of driving &amp;amp; busyness,
mixed with trying to settle emotions stirred up by all the activity.
i don&amp;#8217;t tend to be an extremely emotional person,
so enduring emotional upheaval is a true test of patience for me.
but this unsettlement within me allowed me a window into something i rarely examine:
i was able to tune into how i feel about events, behaviors, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>days #26-#30</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2010/01/31/2010-01-days-26-30-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jan 2010 01:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2010/01/31/2010-01-days-26-30-html/</guid>
      <description>this week has been busy &amp;amp; full of life lessons.
i&amp;#8217;ve traveled to &amp;amp; from tucson (soon to be to &amp;amp; from again),
assisted bob in editing our film to submit to a film festival,
attempted to actually get some work done at the office,
and engaged in a work activity that involved downtown PHX &amp;amp; the light rail.
that last one is what i want to really examine right now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>days #22-#25</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2010/01/26/2010-01-days-22-25-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2010 04:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2010/01/26/2010-01-days-22-25-html/</guid>
      <description>i&amp;#8217;ve been off the grid, indulging a growing passion:
bob, a team of PHX creatives, &amp;amp; i made a full microshort this weekend.
we&amp;amp;#8217;ve been making films together since we met: he directs, i write, &amp;amp; we make magic happen. it&amp;amp;#8217;s tough working so closely &amp;amp; intensely sometimes, and we&amp;amp;#8217;ve learned a lot about teamwork through it all. i guess my passion for making films goes hand-in-hand with my passion for my marriage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>day #21</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2010/01/22/2010-01-day-21-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2010 05:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2010/01/22/2010-01-day-21-html/</guid>
      <description>today is my mom&amp;#8217;s birthday.
she&amp;#8217;s 29 &amp;amp; holding.
if there is anyone in this world who exhibits obvious passion in her life,
it&amp;#8217;s my mom.
mom loves teaching, as well as the kids in her class.
when i call her to catch up, i am always an audience to her stories of their successes or tragedies &amp;#8212;
but most often their successes, since she believes so much in them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>days #19 &amp; #20</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2010/01/21/2010-01-days-19-20-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2010 01:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2010/01/21/2010-01-days-19-20-html/</guid>
      <description>my senses go into overload a lot.
sometimes i get mentally overwhelmed,
and other times i just automatically block out some of the stimuli.
default attention-selection.
today as i walked in the brisk air to the mailbox, i decided to close my eyes.
shutting down that one sense ignited the others!
i felt the subtle breeze &amp;amp; smelled a pre-rain odor.
my tastebuds recalled the soy chai i had earlier.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>days #15-#18</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2010/01/18/2010-01-days-15-18-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2010 16:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2010/01/18/2010-01-days-15-18-html/</guid>
      <description>three-day weekends throw me for a loop.
when i was younger, a day off meant VACATION!
now, it means having more time for organizing, errand-running, &amp;amp; homework.
my to-do list for today looks nothing like a passion-igniter.
but yesterday&amp;#8217;s message at our church certainly was.
after talking about how our small expectations can get in the way of God actually creating something awesome &amp;#8212;
or, at least, get in the way of us appreciating it</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>days #13 &amp; #14</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2010/01/15/2010-01-days-13-14-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2010 14:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2010/01/15/2010-01-days-13-14-html/</guid>
      <description>learning to simplify.
it&amp;#8217;s hard to experience passion when i&amp;#8217;m pulled in numerous directions.
i might mistake the ache of excitement for just an ache of overload &amp;#8212;
if i feel the ache at all.
throughout the past several years, i&amp;#8217;ve been learning about setting boundaries.
this includes knowing my limits &amp;amp; respecting them,
while also pushing those that have growth potential.
this requires some interesting conditional formatting in my life&amp;#8217;s excel table.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>day #12</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2010/01/13/2010-01-day-12-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2010 04:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2010/01/13/2010-01-day-12-html/</guid>
      <description>i decided to inconvenience myself today.
being someone who arranges grocery bags so everything can get carried in on one trip,
plots out maps so all errands can be run in one linear course,
and arranges my schedule to make room for surprises,
i don&amp;#8217;t allow space for inconvenience.
so i suppose i was due some.
the call came as i prepared to tackle a new data analysis project:
i was needed to assist with proctoring an exam.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>days #10 &amp; #11</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2010/01/11/2010-01-days-10-11-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jan 2010 15:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2010/01/11/2010-01-days-10-11-html/</guid>
      <description>i&amp;#8217;m working on a list of passion-blockers.
as i write each one down, i feel a twinge of guilt at how i&amp;#8217;ve let it get to me in the past.
fatigue
denial of ability/passion
fear
resistance
others&amp;#8217; reactions
unrealistic standards
distraction
formalization
and so on&amp;#8230;
my internal conflict comes from my belief that Jesus,
in all His wisdom &amp;amp; love,
has given us all unique passion in each of our lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>day #9: a new face</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2010/01/10/2010-01-day-9-new-face-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2010 01:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2010/01/10/2010-01-day-9-new-face-html/</guid>
      <description>i just wanted to buy some mascara.
i had researched it for months in relation to my preferred mascara brand of several years, the green clinique tube i&amp;amp;#8217;ve perpetually used beyond the recommended 4 months. and as i sat in the chair receiving my impromptu 15-minute makeover, i thought how comparatively impulsive it was for me to agree to this.
the artist, a friendly woman named debbie, worked quickly as she informed me about the various products coating my face &amp;amp; eyes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>day #8: disconnect to connect</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2010/01/08/2010-01-day-8-disconnect-to-connect-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2010 14:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2010/01/08/2010-01-day-8-disconnect-to-connect-html/</guid>
      <description>i like this concept a lot:
&amp;#8220;connecting by disconnecting&amp;#8220;.
i&amp;amp;#8217;ve also been recently made aware of a multi-tasking fast: doing only one thing at a time. mono-tasking. while i don&amp;amp;#8217;t struggle with a crackberry addiction or a need to drown my thoughts with the radio, i do find myself wasting time being too &amp;amp;#8220;plugged in&amp;amp;#8221;. i&amp;amp;#8217;m not certain i could or should unplug completely in today&amp;amp;#8217;s culture, but this article has challenged me to cut back.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>day #7</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2010/01/07/2010-01-day-7-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2010 15:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2010/01/07/2010-01-day-7-html/</guid>
      <description>we ripped 3 links off the blue paper chain hanging in our bedroom this morning. the chain represents our debt, each link being $1,000.
there was a time in my life when spending $1,000 was an absurd thought. however, i came into this marriage with
$7,000 of debt that i owed on my car + $5,000 remaining on my school loan. ____________ $12,000 in the hole.
add that to what bob had being a homeowner with a mortgage, and our chain was too long for us not to notice it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>day #5 &amp; #6</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2010/01/06/2010-01-day-5-6-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2010 15:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2010/01/06/2010-01-day-5-6-html/</guid>
      <description>much of my thinking takes place in the car. i can already predict that &amp;#8212; should a pie chart be made of the topics this blog discusses this year &amp;#8212; a mention of car drives will be a sizable &amp;amp; tasty slice.
as i drove to work yesterday, i found myself really listening to the lyrics on KLove. i saw drivers &amp;amp; landscape around me. colors were vibrant &amp;amp; organic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>day #4: update</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2010/01/05/2010-01-day-4-update-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2010 04:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2010/01/05/2010-01-day-4-update-html/</guid>
      <description>bob has climbed aboard my attempt to mix it up, and we went on our own adventure tonight.
in the 4+ years we&amp;#8217;ve been together, i&amp;#8217;m not sure we&amp;#8217;ve ever &amp;#8220;gone out for a drink&amp;#8221;.
tonight, we took a break from our schedules,
claimed a happy hour,
&amp;amp; descended on sidebar.
we sat on a couch in a dimly lit upstairs bar with no more than 10 other people,
an old kung-fu movie playing on various flat-screens around us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>day #3 &amp; #4</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2010/01/04/2010-01-day-3-4-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2010 14:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2010/01/04/2010-01-day-3-4-html/</guid>
      <description>yesterday, we visited our friends&amp;#8217; church, poiema, one much closer to us than the one we&amp;#8217;ve been attending in north phoenix.
it was odd doing this, as we&amp;#8217;ve been going to PVCC since we moved here, and we&amp;#8217;ve made some great friends there.
still, we were interested in checking out poiema &amp;amp; meeting some new people.
and for those of us who know genesis, our church back in royal oak, you&amp;#8217;d know how at home we felt when we found out the following:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>day #2</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2010/01/02/2010-01-day-2-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2010 16:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2010/01/02/2010-01-day-2-html/</guid>
      <description>it&amp;#8217;s not so much that i was craving tea.
often my cravings force me into a no-nonsense beeline, and, since this was more of a leisurely sunday drive on a friday afternoon, all signs point to no craving.
no, what i was after was more the process than the result. so i embarked on a mini-adventure up the 51, next to the mountains that pop up &amp;amp; appear to swallow cars at shea, heading toward the artsy pedestrian bridges south of greenway.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>first morning</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2010/01/01/2010-01-first-morning-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2010 19:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2010/01/01/2010-01-first-morning-html/</guid>
      <description>i awoke today refreshed &amp;amp; excited to get started on the next 52 weeks. first question to myself: &amp;#8220;how can i be more passionate today?&amp;#8221;
and i found this is harder to answer than i thought. great idea, frustratingly nebulous execution.
so i&amp;#8217;m trying something i don&amp;#8217;t usually do, just to stir things up.
i&amp;#8217;m listing 5 things i&amp;#8217;m grateful for this morning.
 sunshine, bright &amp;amp; warm with a promise of high 60-degree temps today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introducing: PASH10</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2010/01/01/2009-12-introducing-pash10-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2010 01:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2010/01/01/2009-12-introducing-pash10-html/</guid>
      <description>what is PASH10?
i realized that, while i&amp;#8217;m good at setting goals &amp;#8212; and, often, at meeting them &amp;#8212; i haven&amp;#8217;t demonstrated a proficiency in thematic goals. it seems many of my goals are short-sighted &amp;amp; don&amp;#8217;t adhere to a greater strategy.
this year, i named a theme of what i would like to develop in my life over the coming 365 days.
that theme is passion.
passion in my marriage, my faith, my relationships, my interests, my work, my studies, my interactions, and just the way i live my life overall.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>weeding</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2009/05/03/2009-05-weeding-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2009 16:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2009/05/03/2009-05-weeding-html/</guid>
      <description>i&amp;#8217;ve been thinking a lot about weeds,
particularly the ones in the parable of the sower.
in the first two scenarios the seeds didn&amp;#8217;t really get much of a chance:
birds ate &amp;#8217;em or the sun scorched &amp;#8217;em because they didn&amp;#8217;t really have good roots.
but in the third scenario,
the weeds,
the seeds were able to burrow down &amp;amp; begin to grow.
their success was compromised not by the soil but by the setting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>un-compartmentalizing</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2009/01/11/2009-01-un-compartmentalizing-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2009 16:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2009/01/11/2009-01-un-compartmentalizing-html/</guid>
      <description>here&amp;#8217;s my geek moment of the day: i was looking at the word &amp;#8220;Goals&amp;#8221; &amp;amp; realized that if you put the a &amp;amp; l closer to each other&amp;#8230; &amp;#8230;it says &amp;#8220;Gods&amp;#8221;. (which i interpreted to be &amp;#8220;God&amp;#8217;s&amp;#8221;.)
so here&amp;#8217;s why i allowed that thought to take up more than a nanosecond of my time: i have a tendency to keep things separate. i would set my goals for the day, week, month, year, whatever, and then i&amp;#8217;d think, &amp;#8220;oh, i should really include God somewhere in there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>garden talk</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2008/12/27/2008-12-garden-talk-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2008 04:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2008/12/27/2008-12-garden-talk-html/</guid>
      <description>gardening isn&amp;#8217;t really my thing.
still, i&amp;#8217;m fascinated by the thought of mulching.
being able to use the refuse of plants to produce new &amp;amp; healthy plants is so ingenious to me.
and as i ponder this,
i realize that my Gardener is in the business of mulching.
because i&amp;#8217;ve got a ton of refuse that i&amp;#8217;ve accumulated from
 poor choices shameful actions skeletons in the closet  and i often don&amp;#8217;t think anything good can come out of that stuff.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>tidings of joy &amp; suffering</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2008/12/13/2008-12-tidings-of-joy-suffering-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2008 17:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2008/12/13/2008-12-tidings-of-joy-suffering-html/</guid>
      <description>i find it fascinating that this is a season of both
gladness
&amp;amp;
sorrow.
for some, there is gratitude for the gift of life &amp;amp; the opportunity to share all that it means.
for others, there is dread of the stress &amp;amp; sense of inadequacy the commercialized holidays bring out.
for even others, there is a depression that sets in from loss, loneliness, &amp;amp; lethargy.
to reduce/eliminate the holiday blues,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>another gift</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2008/12/04/2008-12-another-gift-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2008 04:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2008/12/04/2008-12-another-gift-html/</guid>
      <description>today, i discovered the trees outside my office building are cottonwood.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>the mouth trap</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2008/11/25/2008-11-mouth-trap-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2008 04:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2008/11/25/2008-11-mouth-trap-html/</guid>
      <description>as i read through proverbs,
there is a lot of attention paid to the mess our mouths can get us in.
gossip, complaining, breaking confidences, &amp;amp; just being stupid,
it&amp;#8217;s all mentioned on the &amp;#8220;avoid&amp;#8221; list.
but, gosh, it&amp;#8217;s so hard to break those habits!
i&amp;#8217;ve been trying to cut down on my negative word quota,
and i&amp;#8217;m finding it would be a whole lot easier if it weren&amp;#8217;t for having other people around.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>leaning on that which stands on its own</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2008/11/18/2008-11-leaning-on-that-which-stands-on-its-own-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2008 03:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2008/11/18/2008-11-leaning-on-that-which-stands-on-its-own-html/</guid>
      <description>it&amp;#8217;s tough to keep track of what i depend on.
i have a list of plans:
plan a, plan b, plan c&amp;#8230;
always something to back up the plan preceding it so i don&amp;#8217;t feel &amp;#8220;out of control&amp;#8221;.
but these plans are really only illusions,
and this gets shoved in my face as often as God remembers to show love to me.
He doesn&amp;#8217;t like me depending on anything other than Him,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>the myth of achieving happiness</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2008/11/12/2008-11-myth-of-achieving-happiness-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2008 14:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2008/11/12/2008-11-myth-of-achieving-happiness-html/</guid>
      <description>when i would ask my clients what they wished to accomplish through therapy,
many shrugged &amp;amp; said half-jokingly,
&amp;#8220;to be happy.&amp;#8221;
it was hard to share in the joke;
happiness doesn&amp;#8217;t really lend itself to creating a clinical treatment plan.
this is why:
happiness is a byproduct of other things, not an end result in itself.
people want it, but we cannot achieve it if it&amp;#8217;s what we&amp;#8217;re pursuing.
i heard a pastor on the radio yesterday remind us of what we should pursue:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>trees &amp; such</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2008/11/08/2008-11-trees-such-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2008 02:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2008/11/08/2008-11-trees-such-html/</guid>
      <description>i&amp;#8217;ve been working with a friend on creating a film piece on trees.
God really seemed to have an affinity to that metaphor.
we&amp;#8217;re finding that we do, too.
the trees of our Lord are sturdy &amp;amp; dependable,
and they are dependent on Him for life &amp;amp; sustenance.
they don&amp;#8217;t run out of fruit &amp;#8212; ever!
and, gosh, does He ever love &amp;amp; care for them.
we&amp;#8217;re excited to make this piece to share His love of trees with others in His forest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>giving thanks when things suck</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2008/10/31/2008-10-giving-thanks-when-things-suck-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2008 00:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2008/10/31/2008-10-giving-thanks-when-things-suck-html/</guid>
      <description>~be cheerful no matter what; pray all the time; thank God no matter what happens. this is the way God wants you who belong to Christ Jesus to live.~
1 thessalonians 5:16-18
it isn&amp;#8217;t easy to be grateful all the time.
my default mode is set to &amp;#8220;brood, worry, &amp;amp; complain&amp;#8221;.
switching out of that mode takes considerable effort.
i mention this because i&amp;#8217;ve been working against my default a lot lately.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>in motion &amp; out of strength</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2008/10/22/2008-10-in-motion-out-of-strength-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2008 05:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2008/10/22/2008-10-in-motion-out-of-strength-html/</guid>
      <description>i heard a comment today that really stuck with me:
God doesn&amp;#8217;t give strength to us when we&amp;#8217;re in motion.
the context of this is NOT that God doesn&amp;#8217;t help us when we have a lot going on.
in fact, the person who said it remarked that God always makes sure we won&amp;#8217;t run out of steam when we are under pressure.
the context of this statement IS that we need to be taking time to be still before God,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>the black hole</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2008/10/16/2008-10-black-hole-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2008 04:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2008/10/16/2008-10-black-hole-html/</guid>
      <description>my mouth gets me into a lot of trouble.
don&amp;#8217;t get me wrong &amp;#8212;
i TRY to make it do good things.
but sometimes it just seems to have a mind of its own.
in reading ephesians 4, it&amp;#8217;s interesting how many things we are warned against that have to do with our mouths.
even the indirect ones, like being angry, are often expressed through words.
so how do we keep our black holes from sucking us into oblivion?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>the dirty rag problem</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2008/10/10/2008-10-dirty-rag-problem-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2008 06:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2008/10/10/2008-10-dirty-rag-problem-html/</guid>
      <description>the first time someone informed me of what &amp;#8220;dirty rags&amp;#8221; translated to in the Bible, it freaked me out.
and i felt really bad about all i was trying to do.
i was one of those kids who liked to work hard &amp;amp; make others proud.
all-american.
good work ethic.
and then i find out that God doesn&amp;#8217;t care about that stuff.
shoot.
i wanted so badly to win His favor with my smart thinkin&amp;#8217;, elbow grease, &amp;amp; lovableness,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>upgrading dream 1.0</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2008/09/26/2008-09-upgrading-dream-10-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2008 17:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2008/09/26/2008-09-upgrading-dream-10-html/</guid>
      <description>i don&amp;#8217;t know why i don&amp;#8217;t get it.
i&amp;#8217;ve gone through it multiple times each year,
but i forget the protocol every time.
God gives me a dream.
i get excited.
i started to dream with this dream.
and this is where i go wrong.
i cling to the dream.
God asks for it back.
i tell him i want to figure it out first, that i have some great ideas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>day 30</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2008/09/19/2008-09-day-30-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2008 14:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2008/09/19/2008-09-day-30-html/</guid>
      <description>we&amp;#8217;re 1&amp;frasl;3 of the way through.
33.3333333333333&amp;#8230;%
but that 1&amp;frasl;3 is just when it comes to time, not to the actual goal.
we prayerfully set the goal of raising $80,000 in 90 days.
the purposes of this goal were to help us:
 get focused on the Lord get out of debt get giving to some important causes.  of course, we realize $80,000 isn&amp;#8217;t petty cash.
so we have been working daily to create new opportunities for cash flow &amp;amp; savings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>a prayer</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2008/09/16/2008-09-prayer-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2008 14:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2008/09/16/2008-09-prayer-html/</guid>
      <description>God, morph me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>the foot bath</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2008/09/07/2008-09-foot-bath-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2008 15:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2008/09/07/2008-09-foot-bath-html/</guid>
      <description>i am fascinated by the thought of Jesus washing feet.
regardless of cultural tradition &amp;amp; symbolism, i just love that this Guy cared SO MUCH about the other guys He hung out with that He took on one of the stinkiest parts of the male body.
that is LOVE.
but here&amp;#8217;s the kicker &amp;#8212;
He tells them that He has to wash all their feet to include them in what He was doing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>unsettling down</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2008/08/31/2008-08-unsettling-down-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2008 16:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2008/08/31/2008-08-unsettling-down-html/</guid>
      <description>i find it funny that i have to ask myself if i want to go deeper with God.
shouldn&amp;#8217;t the answer be an automatic &amp;amp; resounding &amp;#8220;YES!&amp;#8221;?
yet i realize that such a decision creates consequences elsewhere:
going deeper denotes excavation,
and excavation causes other areas to get stirred up &amp;amp; disrupted.
see the helpful flowchart below:
going deeper &amp;#8212;&amp;#8212;&amp;#8212;&amp;gt; knocking my ducks out of a row
i work really hard to get my stuff settled.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>legos</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2008/08/16/2008-08-legos-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2008 14:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2008/08/16/2008-08-legos-html/</guid>
      <description>when i look around at people, i am baffled by the vast array of differences that exist.
sometimes i ask (&amp;amp; have overheard others say),
&amp;#8220;why didn&amp;#8217;t He just make us all alike?&amp;#8221;
and then i see a pack of legos &amp;amp; realize that this is more like how God works.
we are not meant to exist alone.
a solitary lego is of little use other than to hurt a whole lot when you step on it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>kids these days</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2008/08/09/2008-08-kids-these-days-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2008 19:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2008/08/09/2008-08-kids-these-days-html/</guid>
      <description>it was on my first mission trip at age 14 that i realized that being young could be a useful thing.
somehow, i had picked up on the message that a person could not do something of worth until s/he was an &amp;#8220;adult&amp;#8221;.
seeing the zeal of my peers &amp;amp; the products of our Christ-focused teamwork convinced me:
Jesus really can use people under the age of 18!
what bothers me, though, is that there continues to be evidence of reverse ageism when it comes to leadership in the church.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>title of the song</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2008/08/07/2008-08-title-of-song-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2008 03:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2008/08/07/2008-08-title-of-song-html/</guid>
      <description>why would someone who is allergic to cottonwood consider it a blessing?
that&amp;#8217;s what i asked in order to get this exclusive interview&amp;#8230;with myself.
Q: what&amp;#8217;s the story behind the title?
A: i was on a walk in my neighborhood several years ago, frustrated with the pain i was in &amp;amp; my perception of God&amp;#8217;s lack of intervention. i kept chasing after His approval &amp;amp; His gifts, and i came up empty-handed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>being human</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2008/08/03/2008-08-being-human-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2008 02:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2008/08/03/2008-08-being-human-html/</guid>
      <description>know what&amp;#8217;s great about God?
He doesn&amp;#8217;t expect superhumanism.
when He says to get along with others, it&amp;#8217;s always framed in a reasonable manner.
He tells us to take breaks &amp;amp; get rest.
and He only tells us to be peacemakers, not peacekeepers.
i like following a proactive, reasonable, caring Deity.
it makes me want to love Him back.
and keep working at doing what He says,
knowing He&amp;#8217;ll accept me regardless of my imperfections.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>preview</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2008/07/28/2008-07-preview-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2008 00:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/2008/07/28/2008-07-preview-html/</guid>
      <description>en route to church today, i was caught by a thought: i was getting a chance to immerse myself in a preview of Whom i&amp;#8217;d be worshiping.
much like when i was in high school &amp;amp; would listen to every album of the band i was on my way to see in concert. getting to know their work. getting to appreciate their genius. it put me in the right frame of mind to be in awe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creations</title>
      <link>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/creations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jess.bobmarquis.com/creations/</guid>
      <description>Select creations: books, speaking engagements, writings, events, films, and projects.
Books  Meine kleine Einhorn-Farm: Das Standardwerk zur erfolgreichen Aufzucht von Einhörnern, Riva, 2016 Raising Unicorns: Your Step-by-Step Guide to Starting and Running a Successful – and Magical! – Unicorn Farm, Adams Media, 2011  Speaking  CAST #5: Breaking, Fuller Theological Seminary – Arizona, 3.31.18 Silent Light: A Blue Christmas Service, City Square Church, 12.16.17 Formative, Not Definitive: Giving Thanks for It All, City Square Church, 11.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>