<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Unplanned on Jessica S. Marquis</title>
    <link>http://example.org/tags/unplanned/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Unplanned on Jessica S. Marquis</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 31 Jan 2010 01:34:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/tags/unplanned/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>days #26-#30</title>
      <link>http://example.org/2010/01/31/2010-01-days-26-30-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jan 2010 01:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/2010/01/31/2010-01-days-26-30-html/</guid>
      <description>this week has been busy &amp;amp; full of life lessons.
 i&amp;#8217;ve traveled to &amp; from tucson (soon to be to &amp; from again),   assisted bob in editing our film to submit to a film festival,   attempted to actually get some work done at the office,   and engaged in a work activity that involved downtown PHX &amp; the light rail.     that last one is what i want to really examine right now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>days #15-#18</title>
      <link>http://example.org/2010/01/18/2010-01-days-15-18-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2010 16:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/2010/01/18/2010-01-days-15-18-html/</guid>
      <description>three-day weekends throw me for a loop.
 when i was younger, a day off meant VACATION!   now, it means having more time for organizing, errand-running, &amp; homework.   my to-do list for today looks nothing like a passion-igniter.     but yesterday&amp;#8217;s message at our church certainly was.     after talking about how our small expectations can get in the way of God actually creating something awesome &amp;#8212;   or, at least, get in the way of us appreciating it   &amp;#8212; pastor john challenged us to consider some questions during reflection time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>day #9: a new face</title>
      <link>http://example.org/2010/01/10/2010-01-day-9-new-face-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2010 01:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/2010/01/10/2010-01-day-9-new-face-html/</guid>
      <description>i just wanted to buy some mascara.
    i had researched it for months in relation to my preferred mascara brand of several years,   the green clinique tube i&amp;#8217;ve perpetually used beyond the recommended 4 months. 
 and as i sat in the chair receiving my impromptu 15-minute makeover,  
 i thought how comparatively impulsive it was for me to agree to this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>day #4: update</title>
      <link>http://example.org/2010/01/05/2010-01-day-4-update-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2010 04:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/2010/01/05/2010-01-day-4-update-html/</guid>
      <description>bob has climbed aboard my attempt to mix it up, and we went on our own adventure tonight.
 in the 4+ years we&amp;#8217;ve been together, i&amp;#8217;m not sure we&amp;#8217;ve ever &amp;#8220;gone out for a drink&amp;#8221;.   tonight, we took a break from our schedules,   claimed a happy hour,   &amp; descended on sidebar.     we sat on a couch in a dimly lit upstairs bar with no more than 10 other people,   an old kung-fu movie playing on various flat-screens around us.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>