<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Restoration on Jessica S. Marquis</title>
    <link>http://dev.jessicasmarquis.com/tags/restoration/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Restoration on Jessica S. Marquis</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2016 23:06:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://dev.jessicasmarquis.com/tags/restoration/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Church, Please!</title>
      <link>http://dev.jessicasmarquis.com/2016/11/church-please/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2016 23:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dev.jessicasmarquis.com/2016/11/church-please/</guid>
      <description>Dear Bride of Christ,
I love you with a relentless passion that I can&amp;#8217;t abandon no matter how ugly or derisive you become. You are the creation and beloved of my Beloved, and so I am inseparably part of you. So, since I can&amp;#8217;t leave (which is what I&amp;#8217;m best trained in doing), I need to have a literal &amp;#8220;Come to Jesus&amp;#8221; chat with you.
You &amp;#8211; we &amp;#8211; have forgotten our First Love.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Ambivalent Fallout with a Bush: A Story of Unexpected Restoration</title>
      <link>http://dev.jessicasmarquis.com/2016/10/my-ambivalent-fallout-with-a-bush-a-story-of-unexpected-restoration/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2016 03:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dev.jessicasmarquis.com/2016/10/my-ambivalent-fallout-with-a-bush-a-story-of-unexpected-restoration/</guid>
      <description>Last December, we had our front and back yards turned into desert landscaping. They went from being full of dirt, weeds, a big mulberry tree that pigeons pooped from, and a thorny bougainvillea, to being full of rocks, desert plants, a smaller tree that pigeons disdain, and a wispy bush with orange flowers.
We were enamored.
And then the weeds started. They got out of control. We tried to fight them, but we had to have professionals come in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where Are My Eagle Wings?</title>
      <link>http://dev.jessicasmarquis.com/2016/08/where-are-my-eagle-wings/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2016 18:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dev.jessicasmarquis.com/2016/08/where-are-my-eagle-wings/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;#8217;m working hard on CAST #2: Restoration, an event for women focusing on both brokenness &amp;amp; God&amp;#8217;s restorative vision for creation. My personal drama is this: I&amp;#8217;m currently in a complicated relationship with restoration.
As I&amp;#8217;ve previously written, I recently went through a confusingly dry season of waiting &amp;amp; clinging. It&amp;#8217;s been jet-black darkness at countless times, with equally innumerable false-starts of returning to daylight.
All the while, I&amp;#8217;ve been holding to the hope-inflating notion that when I reach daylight there will be a tangible sense of restoration.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>